Hello, having a little beautiful day. It's like the weather was just me for me today.
It's been beautiful. A beautiful neighborhood. Yeah, I actually, I mean, I don't think I could
have picked a better place to have been born, but I don't think I don't know if I picked it.
I think I was just born here, right? Sometimes we don't know exactly why we're born in the
circumstances we are. I do know one thing. It's like sometimes we don't attract the people.
Re-attracting to our life we're attracting lessons and so nothing need to look at this lesson
And some of these lessons are very difficult. Oh shit, or they can be very difficult, but you know what once you actually learn something
That cannot be taken away. Hold on a second. It's brick wall right here. Okay. I do
shit
My gosh
Thank you
Hi, we're back. I
I'm outside. I'm outside. What's up? Who's that? Let me see that bubbles
Yes, Bubbles. What's up?
Hold on, I need to turn my camera on.
Sorry. Let me see.
Where is it? I'm almost home though.
Hold on. I think I touched the button.
There I am. Okay.
Yeah, I am outside here.
You see?
Beautiful, beautiful day.
Yeah, what I was just thinking, I was like...
You know, people say there's something
called white privilege, but...
I think I've seen plenty of whites that you would not consider privileged.
I've seen plenty of blacks that you would consider affluent, and many other races.
So I think we're getting away from this racial stuff, but there's still going to be people
stuck in the past, you know, fixated on race, and race really isn't.
It's like, you know, okay, I can go to skin color, I can go to ethnicity background,
but at the end of the day, we're human beings, we're all human.
We're playing in water right now, look at this screen, beautiful.
Yeah, but, um, well, I'm happy about, you know,
we are in this wild, wild West on YouTube,
and there's, like, really, what are the rules?
I mean, the rules are there really are no rules,
but I like to take a few things seriously.
Like, for example, I always thought, like,
you know, YouTube and media is a way to, you know,
get out messages, and I also have done a marketing.
as a CEO for, um, as an assistant to the CEO for a, um, Fortune 5 pun.
Okay, here I am.
So there's a few things I was walking at that I came to my mind.
And there are a couple of Tupac songs.
One of them is Me Against the World.
What is Me Against the World?
One of them was, uh, Only God Can Judge Me, right?
We have, uh, we have a lot of people.
Oh, shit.
You see me?
Why am I I can see myself with it? Why can't I see myself here like this? Okay. Here I am, but
Yeah, I mean it's like I
There are judges in the world and we appoint these judges actually because it's like if everyone was allowed to judge I
mean people would be pretty fucked because the
people taking the law into their own hands keep people taking the
Highland or
um
the judgment into their own hands and and also
speaking for God, like, oh, well, this God of this religion is on my side, and here's
what he's going to do to you, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I mean, that's what we do as humans, because, you know, sometimes we do feel powerless in
circumstances.
That's why magic isn't here in the first place.
It's to give people that had, felt like they had no power, some kind of power over their
Um, I know that there's a book called, um, it's an Italian, but it's the Italian book
about Diana, um, oh, Aradia, Aradia, have you heard of Aradia?
So Aradia is like this Italian daughter of Diana, and she comes to Earth basically to
teach magic and to, um, and sometimes magic was about, you know, because they, you know,
Like, you know, like, still like, like we do today, there's like, you know, there's a few people at the top of the pyramid, and then it goes a few more people with each rung down, and then finally, you know, the masses and the slaves on the very bottom, right?
I don't like, I don't even like, you know, I like to think that we're done with slavery, right? I mean, but no, we're really not.
You side with Moses and Elijah? Yeah, I do too. I mean, over Jezebel? For sure, for sure.
And Elijah was just John, you know, or John was Elijah, I guess Elijah came first, right? Yeah,
Elijah was John, he was his reincarnation. And so, and, you know, prophets and stuff like that.
Oh, baby. John was interesting because he basically had a diet of like wild roots and
She's possessed by a demon. She is a demon. I'm not sure. I don't know
you know
like usually
You know even in this community, which I think it's pretty bad
I know people have done stuff
But it's like the only story I've heard about people with dogs and kids or like people's dead parents and stuff is like, you know
basically her
Right, and so are we surprised now?
Is it appropriate? Well, and then okay, well the further thing is I'll address some things like I'm being said
Oh, I took advantage of her grieving her father who died of cancer last year. My father died of cancer two years ago
I'm still grieve my father
But she's taking advantage of me. Can I say the same thing?
when I
You know, I didn't really do anything. I don't yeah, how am I okay? Hi goal. Hey boy. How are you? Good to see you here?
you're a good you're a good mod so don't mind I'll mod you up um but I mean it's like I mean if you
saw I mean gosh I mean it's like I don't know if I talk about her she gets mad if I don't talk about
her she gets mad and so I mean I'll talk about her if she were mad anyway right but um so I uh
there's a saying like you know first they came for the communists and they came for the
for these people and then they came for the Jews and no one said anything and they came for me
Right, and it's like who's in who's in a computer? Who are they gonna come for after me?
They're gonna come for you and so it's like, yeah, I'll be in this position right now of like, you know
The one everyone can laugh at mock. I'll be a pebble across for a second
But just remember once I once I'm gone. There's another sacrifice. It's gonna be needed, right?
I mean, it's like, you know, they're not satisfied with just Jesus.
I mean, they apparently need tons of sacrifices all the time.
I mean, but the crops got to grow, right?
Um, I mean, it's like how, how wacky people are.
I mean, it's just like, you know, and I'm both, I'm in both sizes, extremes and stuff.
But, uh, basically, I, I mean, I've been so called, oh my gosh, and there's, okay, so.
Well, yeah, so clumsy writes I bet she is very proud of me right okay
Let me see with mr. Extendall grooming is disgusting 20 plus years in difference by the way
Let me see there's no there's 19 years in difference. I am 45 Joker is 26 and so that is 14 years
Well, is that 20 years? Hold on
19 years
Joker and I are not dating
But there's something wrong and Joker and like, you know, I've laughed around with Joker
But yeah, okay, anyway
But you know what he got mad because I said he could take a broom not a joke when he types Joker
He's he's you're grooming that's disgusting as fuck. You know it's disgusting as fuck clumsy
Child endangerment getting into a high-speed chase with police with your toddler in the car
I mean is that that's a height a responsible parent came
Go stick another don't you think stick a vacuum cleaner of your butt? Okay, and take that and take that next
I know a broom's not even enough for you. You lousy filthy
Whatever you are man, okay. Well, I don't want to get
Too off but it's but yeah, but of course. Yeah, okay, so let's get but let's get everybody's um, yeah
Well, we're so bad, but it has to be fair. So how would they?
What kind of scum bag does this while driving? Yeah, Joker's a 20. Yeah, it's grown adults plus
There's not what there's not any kind of you're never met or anything. It's like I mean, it's what I mean, so
J. Howard Marshall. He was like 90 something years old. Anna Nicole Smith was 25. That's 75 years old
What do people say about that? Yeah, go Anna. You know, it was like it was
you know, what about Martha Ray and
Mark Harris
You know, that's like a 90 year old woman a man in his 20s or 30s. All right
70 years. What did they say about that? Not really much either because no one really
I'm gonna give us a fuck once you get over like
In like the 25 mark basically we're adults. We can make our own decisions, right? He was a sad story
She was I think there's a really good. Um
There's a thing on Netflix. I don't know if it came out yet, but this kind of reminds me of like kind of the message
I want to send to you. Hold on. I
Think it's called like from to Anna with love or format from Anna with love or something. Oh, no, it's called. You don't know me
So this is this uh
Yeah, you don't know me
So this is a preview of this movie and I'll I'll get you a look at you. I'm just gonna eat my page
I want to give vulgar vulgar look look at what they say for being here. I know see man
Everyone's I mean
It's you have to be great to be brave to come here. You have to be brave so but no, I will have your back here
What's that money for 20? Okay?
She died. Yeah, I got you. Okay. I'm gonna mod. Okay mod. Okay. I don't know why you're not a mod here
It is that here it'll play this there you go standard. Hey, okay, and I think Lava said he didn't want one
But if you do let me know okay, so
She died right after son. Yes, she did and she's probably in grief
And you know there are people that go through grief and you know sometimes are bad
There are people that take advantage of people that are going through grieving
and I know because I feel like I've been taking advantage of in
In my grieving process because I just want to say one thing I never
I never, I'd like to produce any proof of me asking her for a dime ever.
Ever. And I want to, I can show you all, all she could be able to produce is me
proof, like profusely thanking her. You know who I'm talking about, right? For,
for whatever she sent, right? And it's very generous. But the thing is, it's like,
there's, there's something called like, you know, gifts with strings attached, I guess,
There's something like that maybe maybe going on with there too because you know
I'm just the more I watch that first episode when she's trying to say the N word you get my
Over and over she started saying N and then and then and then and then over and over and she's like oh
You don't care about your friends. Uh your friends show are you like you know, they are you really are these friends with her now?
You know by the way are these
RG actually she made up with Bita Kate or you know, she's trying to she's she apologized to everybody
You know except for me. I'm now I've been put in that devil role. I mean, she's taken every person. She's hey
I put it all on me
Do what do to me worse than anybody you've ever done be things beyond
morally ethically spiritually
They're wrong and you don't have the higher ground here because what you have the you have so the some troll community all excited about it
I mean you on oh
Please and then as for judgment about what I do for a living. I mean ma'am
You took cock for a living. I mean seriously that was and you're I mean it's fine
I haven't I've never had a judgment about it, but it's like
I mean, if you can do that, can I try to make a living doing YouTube and aren't there some
jobs that is like, or some career paths that actually, you know, you have to build over
time and sometimes they might not even work.
There's people like go to Hollywood their whole life trying to become a, you know, the
next star, right?
Yeah, she really does.
And yeah, I won't get too much into it, but yeah, it's all being, it's all being very
I'll just say I mean, how would she like I mean, it's like really funny, too
It's like, you know, I mean and I won't I mean because you know
She doesn't mind sharing all my private conversations or the fact that she's been even been here
It's like the prop pretending that she doesn't know anything about it
And but she's been here and stuff like that or you know, so it's like yes
I mean a huge mistake because I
I love, I trust, if I didn't, would I disclose anything?
I mean, it's like, if I was a scam artist,
wouldn't I just lie about everything?
But I'm still, everyone's not banned.
I see you, Psyche's realities.
Everyone's not banned.
I went through my list.
If you have a problem with someone that's banned,
you can just let me know their name in the chat.
Oh, look, there's Brandon Q.
Well, Brandon, you're banned from the chat,
so I never want to see you here.
Why don't you go to your own lane stream?
Okay, bye, and why don't you leave too?
You know what, you know why everyone if everyone's banned if I wanted to ban everybody
You know I could do that. That's another thing with YouTube people seem to think that it's like oh, it's ours
Like it's it's it's the chap it belongs to the chat. It belongs
What is the tea? Okay? Yeah, well the situation is
You know, there's a very controversial
streamer
That
I was friends with me. She came she appeared on my show
We have the same birthday and had his mother's stuff then come in and I liked her a lot and months
We were friends then over like something very very trivial
She turned on me all of a sudden the next day. I'm a human trafficker. I'm a spiritual trafficker
I'm an abuser and blah blah blah blah blah and people people like to run with these things, right?
Is is be a brand I know is any terrible and I never did anything that him either all I did was let out
I I fucking took so much shit
just to let him have someone, like, you know, let him speak his mind, and because people that
were telling me, no, you know, they were not my friends, you know, and so I needed, and plus
one thing about me is like, I will let people up, but if they are bad, I mean, they'll reveal that
they're bad, and it's like, and then I've done a service actually, so why be mad at anybody I have
in my show, I don't understand people, but so the chat seems to, like sometimes the chat thinks that
I'm their monkey or their puppet or there's something and you know
They don't they have they ever like most of them 99% ever done one thing for me besides just troll me and say terrible things
And spread rumors and slander, but no, I mean it's like
You know most of it, but then they want to
Tell me who to block on blog and you know, so let me just worry about those things. Okay. I have mods taking care of it. Yeah
And, I mean, it's like, you know, he can't, I mean, he's, I mean, he, I don't know if it's trauma anymore, because he's just, he does very stupid things like he, he basically was given a mea culpa, he was given forgiveness.
A low cow is a bad thing to be I know it is because that's, but that's like the part of the culture is like people thinking of this thing I'm trying to change this part of the culture because I'm most of these low cows are just people that are like been so retarded or obese and, you know, these kind of things.
People like to laugh at you know the obvious things or whatever but the thing about the locust thing is that people actually will treat it
like a video game and try to like
get in there and
He starts yeah, he starts at a zillion. Well, it's him and his you know his his army. He's an army of robots, you know
They should be called branding cubots
But that's that's his that's his fan base is you know
Robots
That's his echo chamber because some people need to feel powerful
I mean I know like there are bots in my check cuz he was buying them. I didn't buy I never asked him for I didn't do anything
And it's like but he would he would put him in here when he came in so then he could say oh, I'm I made your show
I you know
But you pay that you paid a dollar for 50 bots for an hour or something. I mean it's like
It's like whatever it's like. I'm not even honest. I don't I don't really care about numbers or anything
I do this just for fun, but it's like when it gets to the point where it's like
I'm being put in danger and and other people are being put in danger because people
Are psychotic and evil
Because I was nothing but nice and
But anyway the second time well, so then anyway, we made up, you know, so it was like, you know
He not make my show. My show got, you know, most people, you know, a lot of people left
this show because he showed up and I've gotten fights with people over him. People have the
main characters. Yeah, but they can be the main, the whole thing is you can be the main
character on your own show. People, anybody can make a channel, except, you know, some
people, like, you know, some people can't, you have to go to rumble and stuff. But most
people can make a channel on YouTube, right?
Put whatever they want on it, and then they can make it 50 people they can have a chat and then they can run it
How they want and then they and then oh, so I don't like to be told what to do
especially by people that don't have a channel or
You know don't and these are the people that are usually trying to tell you what to do, right?
But like I said, it's like I don't I didn't sign like something I signed when I was a YouTube partner
It was a deal with YouTube. It wasn't a deal with the audience. It's not like and so it's like I I'm not here to be
I'm here to entertain and as I get people want to watch they can watch if they don't want to watch it's fine
I don't care if there's five people in here
I don't care if there's a hundred people in here
It's fun if there's a high energy
But it'd be just as fun if those five people are the great conversation going on as opposed to like a hundred people just just being trolls
Right, it's like and then it's all they try to do is distract and basically get you out of your emotions and stuff
So I'm very calm right now, and I'm very interested in my legal rights and
Listen listen
I guess that there's a saying that when your enemy is making a mistake, don't correct them.
But maybe that's even too much to say, you know, maybe it's a little hint.
Drama is fun. Yeah, but you know, high drama panels are very easy to crash out on or to burn out on
They have a very high burnout rate
And so because when you sit there for hours and hours, there's people arguing just to get a psychological
subconscious thing of all these arguments
All day all day all day and then it's like kind of like it goes Gino or Gigo garbage in garbage out
Yeah, I have to be my own drama came go too far. Oh, yeah, it then goes too far and I mean there's accusations man
I mean the good thing the positive thing is that first of all the other person's behavior is just very well-documented and
Especially with the codex number. It's all very well-documented and everything that happened and every
It's very clear. I mean it's like in the thing if you don't think that
If you think that I actually did something, I mean, if you believe the allegations and I mean if these allegations were true
I would definitely not even be jail. I think I'd be an electric chair gas chamber or something
I mean, I think the allegations that have been made on me are like so criminal. It'd be federal prison. It would be
And I've never had anything beyond a mystery number just basically a speeding ticket, right?
Even if I didn't spend a day or two in jail, right?
It's just it was for misdemeanor. I would have oh shut up Brandon
It and that brand that minor mod of course was Brandon pretending to be either pretending to be a 12-year-old girl
Or he talks to 12 year-old girls and says can you can you try to be a modern psyche's chat and look at all them?
All the bots are coming at the exact same time. Oh, you bought some bots Brandon really really impressive
Okay, he's a cool minor. He spelled it. Am I any are?
He spells it. Am I any are yeah?
That's how he that's how he actually spelled it on his post and so all this stuff about oh, he's so intelligent
It's because he wears glasses doesn't mean he's smart. He's pretty much
You know has the you know
the brain of a mushroom
You know and not one of the good ones like the
But when it's fucking fungus that grows up of cow shit basically, okay?
Anyway, you're a bot KZ. I know you are
That's why everyone
Well, why aren't you in jail? Are you the Gabriel KZ? Well, let me look at that picture
You go back to jail Brandon made me. Yeah, he made he
What he made he made a
He made me unpopular
Yeah, he kind of he did it for a day. But you know, okay, look at all the bots guys. Look at how sad he is
He's so sad. He's so focused too. He just needs this. He needs this. Yeah. Oh Brandon. Yeah, he's just so stupid
Oh, yeah, because all these people this is the Q army, right?
Robots coming in saying the exact same thing at the exact same time with no context and they have you know, no history
I mean Brandon give a life
For you lose your channel again. I mean jeez such a loser
All Brandon does is goes to truth finder, which is like all publicly available information
He goes to and then he buys his bots from I guess like the Cleveland bot factory or something. I don't know even
Docs himself about it. Oh, I'm a crack it down. You're not the real Crack-a-dona real crack-a-dona has some sense
He wouldn't be Crack-a-dona too. You're a weirdo
Bye and hey, we are the weirdos mister. Oh Brandon made me. Oh, this is funny. Hey guys. Oh, yeah
Guys, can you a bull goes a minor? Oh my gosh. Well Joker and I are in big trouble, right?
Yeah, exactly. Don't use Volga's name in vain
Yeah, how about this let's watch this video of Brandon
Flirting with with minors on the monkey up. How about let's watch that
That'd be a fun thing to watch so we never really watch close enough, you know, I think I should watch that finally
So let me see
Okay, so I think it's like Brandon Hugh loves kids or something like that. It's the channel one second oopsie
Hey, I'm you know, it's like if you don't want to take it don't dish it out Brandon
But he also he feeds into this this thing too because he he's like I'm outside your daughter's window club
I mean he's like he's just it's perverted and I was like I think he's
Just insane. Okay, so I don't even see that website anymore. Okay, so let me see
I know it's on my last discord. Oh, yeah, let's see. Well, it says he's talking clumsy son, but I don't play that one
We see
Okay
Well, can someone give me that that link please if they know or I mean, I know that those videos are around
I just can't find them right now
Okay. Well, anyway, we'll play that later as soon as I soon as someone sends it to me someone send it to me, right?
Hold that L boy
Whatever happened to Gotti Gotti's around still. Who's my friend big rum horn?
Just get mods. Can you just like if you see a Brandon bot? Can you just delete it, please?
We're gonna be a brand-in-free zone from now on unless we're like, you know, you defend it and support a brand
I'm every after seeing I know I've not ever seen how sick I was because
And that went, hold on, that won't be forgotten,
you were a sick freak too, okay?
Well, how about, so you think the same thing
about Alexandra because do you remember
that she, you don't have the link, okay?
Alexandra actually called me onto the show,
oh, can you help redeem Brandon and stuff?
And she was like, Brandon's very handsome
and Brandon's so smart.
And so is anybody mad at her about it?
No, even RG was like, oh, psyche, boycott.
And he's over there on her panel.
And so is that, like, what is that?
Is that a, what is it, hypocrisy?
Apocrisy?
And, you know, basically, you both, yeah, we both,
yeah, and I, guys, I made a mistake.
She says, she blames me for her doing it.
She's like, oh, you made me do that.
And now people are, now he's blowing up at me.
So she blames, so it's gonna be my fault at the end, right?
But.
It's yeah, exactly and because he would have left but then she kept coming in like making an issue and then I think she had a plan to like
Basically get all these enemy all these people that like didn't like her
Under her side through the situation
Karen and Alice were right about me
What oh please oh?
They were they were there so
Alice was right
Oh my gosh, well, if you want to see if you want to know more about Alexandria, you know, of course, just go to QE farms
Look up Monica Foster, Alexandra Mayers. She is very heavily documented there as a also is a homophobe too
And that's interesting with a gay father
What was the idea behind my Lucifer stigial and any other stigials? Okay?
Because I have an idea I have a certain idea of things. Okay, so it's like, you know, there's
The satanic idea, which is like it was very negative thing, but there's also like the similar
Christ idea to it, which is light, right? And
And I think light allows vision and so even like the sim vestigial is also represents like the
how the eye works and so
But there's also a thing called the evil eye, right?
You know also think which is like basically if someone's envious of you or jealous
That's the root. That's kind of the root of all of the evil eye, right? I'm with the link KZ. Okay
Yeah, and obviously it's being used on me right now. I mean, it's like there's enough to say about me that is
That you can like, you know, be as controversial. Oh, he's gay. He's this is that you know, it's dirty
But so much is being said that it's so beyond that and then it's like an even going to like
Oh, my parents, they are terrible parents and stuff like that.
Well, do you know, like even like,
like first of all my parents were wonderful parents.
Like they're very wonderful parents.
And I thought anything I was,
I was the difficult one, not them, hold on.
The UKZ, hold on.
No, they're good parents.
It's like, but you know,
our parents responsible necessarily for 100% or 100%
how the kids always turn out.
It's like, no, not necessarily the court
because we're different people.
We are different people, right?
But if you don't know my parents and you don't know me you have no place to speak on it
And just like I don't I would have a place to speak on it. You know, it's like a yo mama joke. Basically. Okay
So that's a fake account. Hey move goo goo goo. No
Type in the bag chat who you are if I know you but you're probably just, you know branding huge
Okay, oh he's going move goo goo goo like I'm like a laughing cow and his name is C
Bowl G bull
G bully. Okay
Oh, he's talking in private chat. He says, wow, I ain't fucking Brandy Q
That's nothing Brandy Q would say
Right. He would actually come up on a
Someone would come up with that with their face showing the way come up. It's like some yeah
It looks like either Brandy Q or the regular Q, right?
lowercase Q
one of the two
Q balls. Oh
There is another account. Okay, so obviously okay, so someone comes right back when I kicked him out of the studio
Obviously it's not what is the center's name now it says G bull
Okay, I mean, oh, okay. No, there's Volga. Okay. Hold on a second. Are you Volga?
Okay, here they left. Okay one second. I'm gonna put my banner up
Volga
Why do you have a minor mod Volga's a child?
We have a minor my guys can someone give me that video, please
Can you give me the video of Brandon Q talking to like I'm hitting on mine or saying he wants to have sex with a 12-year-old
Can someone give me those videos, please?
Yeah
I gave you the evil eye, I'm a hater.
I gave it to you.
Yeah, he's upset.
I mean, it's like, they're basically,
they'd be a cute couple.
Imagine the kid though.
Oh my God, it'd be insane.
It'd be an insane pedophile kid, you know?
Let's see, now he's texting me.
Probably Tony, let's see what it says.
Tony also, by the way, is a locale, you know, officially.
He actually like I'm looking at range. Oh, he's good. I'm confirmed and verified predator lover
Okay, then he puts picture of Minnie Manson's vagina. So it's Tony
Okay, I would show it but Minnie Manson's vagina showing
BQ is a PDF. That sounds like something BQ would say. Let me see Johnny skin Diffie. Tell me who you are
Are you you're not the sage? Are you?
That's Moogoo Google saying that so I mean
I don't know, just come as yourself, moogoo-goo-goo.
I don't know who you are.
I don't want to have some random person.
I already got, I already got Brandon up thinking he was Volga.
Yeah.
And Volga is not a minor.
So you're all you're just gonna say that cuz you're just so now you're but her brand and you're just random but hurt
They should well be John. John. You're not Jewish. Stop pretending John. John. Did you hold on?
Beedah was right
Beedah was right. Beedah is so vindicated. She has proved
She's a much better person than you by far Christine to be Dan Christine were so right the copyright strikes are on their way
It's time to get you offline
I'm so scared
Oh, what? I have to leave YouTube. Oh my God. So sad.
I'm only here because I have a point to make still.
Um, yeah. And yeah, he has actually been indicted for harassment.
Oh, Joker went live last night and has an open panel.
It would have been cool if I had gone on.
I did go on live. I mean, he's been on my show, Nick.
He's been on the show recently, like several times,
and I went on last night for a minute.
But then he had this guy on.
It's kind of weird. I was kind of weird. I don't know. I like he was nice, but
And guys just here the only thing you need to do with a mod
There's two things you have to do if you see someone if you see Brandon Q or Tony in the chat or RG
There is you got it. If you see it was on the other channel cuz I'm on my new channel
You see Tony or do whatever or
What's his name Brandon?
Just can you can you just hide them for me so we don't have to like you know go over it?
Yeah, I mean what's this person saying makes me fall so let me see six things urban magoo
I'm not Brandon a I my motherfucker eat shit thinking I'm Brandon Hugh fuck you well
I don't know who you are, but you have fifth sages picture you come up as moogoo goo goo and you come up as
Some other name. What's I don't know what the name it says it says you are
Johnny skin
Johnny Skandisky, I don't know
But just because I think I mean if you're wrong, I mean it's like I'm not something like doesn't make you him
Yeah, he is a creeper at home. Yeah
Why don't you just participate in chat if you have something to say you have to come up on panel and do something
I don't understand
Brandon's just oh my god
First I thought like I was like bulldozer like bulldozer kermit the frog and I was like, oh, it's
Oh, then no, then I actually thought it was Peewee Herman, but uh, this is Brandon
Oh
My gosh, I need to do that. That'd be such a funny AI. I'm gonna put Brandon and a pee we heard my outfit
Would that be funny? I'm gonna do it right now. Let me see
Yeah, let's picture
We can find it. Oh here we go. Let me see the guests
Okay, okay, let me just check. Okay, but you you can come on but okay
What?
Unven moogoo-goo-goo now nigga
This stage
Unvail me go go go now nigga. Don't call me and word and donate to me and now I'll do it like
There you go. Okay
Here's an apology
Or just be on this one. I don't know. Okay. Now. It says stage. Okay, so what?
What you're on the air
Okay, stage he's off. I mean jeez
jeez Louise
Yeah, but it's really funny. It's but it's like, you know, what's really funny is the projection that goes on
I'd actually did a great presentation or projection
Which is there's a lot of in this community sometimes where it's like
Call everyone else, but you are right as projection basically is or just make up a lie, too
I mean people do lie to you about it, right?
Yeah, he does he does I'm gonna put up
Okay, hold on hold on I'll ban the fucking moogoo goo, but you better be nice to me. Hold on
What was it? G ball or bomb? Okay. Okay. I am banned G ball if you want to go on that account. It's unbanned
It's unbanned
Do we know unbanned fifth through 85th stage as well?
You say just burped. Oh my god. Here he is. Okay. Oh my god. Hi, Lenar. Let's see. Hold on once again
You're on the air. How's it feel psyche dealing with all the bullshit and backlash as you deserve. I
deserve it
Yes, you protected a predator. You turned against everybody who supported you. No, you were stuck it off a predator
You were telling you were following I and X and everybody else
She still sucks off Brandon she still sucks off the predator and you protected them and welcome them with open arms to the point
We're now Alex is sitting here showing your parents and Alex is not going to stop
I
Don't care about your family. I'm telling you what you opened up
I mean what is it? It's like I've already said I made a mistake
I mean it's like what someone told because someone has something on their show they deserve
They deserve that right?
What's not cool?
What's not cool KZ you I know you're not cool
You don't have to, Sage is a bitch, a little bitch.
Because you know, anybody else, it wasn't open arms,
it was like, it was because I was like, you know,
Tony and like, you know, people were like,
oh, don't do this, do this, and I've been through
so many things with LD and even KZ.
KZ, remember when people say, don't have KZ on
because he spit on a pregnant woman?
And I was like, well, I need the paperwork.
And then there was police reports.
And I was like, well,
It's not like, you know, the spit, like, you know, killed the baby or something like that.
I don't know.
It didn't seem like the hugest deal to me, so I still have him on.
And then everyone got over it.
I didn't know Brandon Q was such a fucking retard, okay?
I mean, now I know, but he has the, you know, like, aww.
It's like, you know, when he has the kind of like, or like, so retarded, it makes you
feel sorry for them for a second.
I'm stupid.
Like, you know, that's why I play the snake.
I'll play the snake again.
I mean, it's like, I'll play this song though, hold on.
Al Jolson, don't call me please.
Oh, hold on, hold on, I should.
Hold on, no, I see who it is, okay.
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oh, I'll be right back.
Yeah, RG told everyone Casey's dead and stuff like that.
But look, I haven't, I, whatever.
So, like I said, I was wrong about Brandy Q.
I was wrong about Alexandra.
Fuck!
I mean, I might be wrong about a lot of people.
You know, it's like, I don't necessarily, you know,
sometimes people are, you know, good actors.
Maybe I'm just dumb.
I don't know.
But at the end of the day, I have like a heart that's like,
I'm not gonna like, just give up on people
and there's probably a good part in everybody.
I'm kind of changing my mind now.
Maybe Alex Downer's right, where it's like,
maybe some people are just garbage.
And no matter, you know, they're gonna be,
they're gonna be a bum on the street, right?
What is this a close race? Oh fuck. There's something close racism. I learned it from her. She taught me that word
To airs human. Hey, how much forgive is divine? How about like didn't and all I have who miss Christian too?
Isn't miss Christian aren't it? This is a this is a this is a former porn star Bible reader who's sitting there reading
This is Bible, right? So she's the moral. She's the moral arbiter of the future, right?
We're just gonna have porn stars as the as the minister from now on
See that thing is that's fine actually because it's like there can be like
People that find god in jail and things like that, but you can't say I found god and then
totally first of all
You you can't first of all then you can't hate the jews right like she does
And and make a big deal out of every jewish person right because of this and this and this right
Hey Arthur, what's up because jesus was jewish
Jesus was Jewish. You know, he's the Hebrew. Okay, so he wants another chance. Okay, I'll give him one more chance because I'm stupid
But we'll see. Okay
What you think I can just tell by his tone that he wasn't gonna be nice. It was it was the asshole sage again
So if he wants to say something to me, he can say it to me
To a private message or something. You don't have to come up here and monopolize my platform
Go over to your girlfriend Kate or um, you know your girlfriend salmon or something like that. I don't know go go glaze somewhere else
Like, my show's not about just pleasing fucking the worst of the worst trolls.
It's basically about hopefully helping some people, but entertaining at least.
But it's not going to stop.
Well, you know, either they stop or they'll be made to stop.
How about that?
You cannot hate Jews, people, of course, they get a lot of hate, but if you are calling
who was a Hebrew and a rabbi. Oh, look at this. Support it. Okay. So there's, look at that.
So that's, so I don't know. It's like, it's like spit salt. I don't know. It was a legal gray area for me.
I'll remember this well because you come on with the attitude and you're coming on disrespectfully and in case you continue to do that
Oh, there's beta. Oh, there she is laughing. So let's see. Oh, you know beta is friends with Alex now, you know, you know Alexander
You know, beta. Oh, of course, you know, beta was like, oh
She's like now she's like saying oh Alex and an ex is so stupid because she thinks you did cocaine. Oh, yeah
anyway
Yes, you can you you cannot hate the Jews and say you love Jesus because Jesus was Jewish
Isn't this funny here? Here's here's here's here's the whole thing with beta like look
This is like, you know that when time she came on like drunk on my show and started screwing my mom and my mom and stuff
Which is where Alexander got half her stuff just copies beta because she's so jealous of beta's audience
So let's let me just look at I lost that picture of shit. I used to have it. Hold on. Let me get down
Um, it's just on, you know, it's on Devilize.
Devilize is just, um, what's his name?
It's, uh, Barry. Barry the Turtle is, um...
as a devil eyes and so they made me look like
basically Edward scissor hands or like, you know
Freddie crew verse on the Abbey's this you yeah, exactly. I'd be huge long nails all during and then it's like and then they put her
You know, she called it so drunk she didn't remember but she said and stuff like that or didn't even realize the window was broken
But she's like sitting there like if she's not even I mean really her picture is like some kind of like
Airbrush high school photo of herself or something like that where I don't even know it does not look like her at all
I mean, I've seen her picture. She looks she looks like a witch
I mean like not not the good kind like the wicked the wicked kind from the Wizard of Oz right not glinda
Go away stage. Like you have nothing good to say, but you're still you're still bitching backstage. You just go bitch backstage
Thank you. He left finally. He said I'll be nice and you're not gonna be nice
You're mean and you're and I didn't ask you sure like to say what she said and so
Yeah, I mean it's like
But uh, yeah, I mean my at this point my biggest, uh, okay. We'll see you have one more chance
I'm gonna ban your account again if you keep bucking with me. Okay, so one second
What? Thank you. Yeah, I'm trying to be nice to you. You weren't trying to be nice. You're like saying
No, you don't tell me to lower my tone. I'll tell you what no, no, you don't talk to me. That's not polite
You're being very rude. You're very rude. No, I'm gonna ban all I'm gonna ban 75 through 100 stays back
You already have you need to unbanned them or else
Or else you're not because you're a pedophile nigger lovin faggot
Well, okay, so I'm just first of all I figured out how to like how that doesn't matter on YouTube if you say that
Guys, that was an example of the disgusting
idiocy and ignorance and stupidity of
Some people in modern America and he was demonstrating that and can we just feel sorry for that kind of person that I would say such a thing because
Obviously that person is mentally deranged
You know
Sad sick
Probably very very lonely, you know. Yeah. Oh my devil eyes as a female. No, no, no
It's like he's doing the poor people.
Hey, hey, RG, I thought you didn't like people
that had brand new cue on why you're on Alexander's program.
I don't understand.
Glazing her.
It was retarded.
It's like so weird.
Yeah, so, yeah.
I mean, geez.
ARG, but yeah, I would recommend. Yeah, and RG is right there in her chat like very excited
I mean he's he doesn't see that that's just proofs. He doesn't care about the kids
Right and most of these people even have kids that are like screaming so loud about no
They're just like screaming about it because it gets attention and because because it gets people riled up and stuff
And it was an effective tactic to use at some point because the society's kind of gone cuckoo for cocoa puffs, but
Now it's well all it really did is weaken the whole the whole like the whole real system and you know against it
Yeah, okay, so I'm just gonna keep banning this person. He just keep coming back up. Okay. He ran away. I
Mean I gave ample opportunity. They can't say I don't give chance after chance after chance, right?
hoping you know it may be insanity because it's like you know, but uh
chance to chance after chance after chance
Even I still have sick on the show. I mean, I've banned him from the show probably 50 times
So I know I don't have a great track record
But at the same time, is that really flip-flopping? No, because I never like really hated these people
Okay, I see you. I see you. Tell me you're sorry. No, no
Tell me you love me. Why did you leave me all alone?
Why did you call me a PDF and an n-word on my phone?
You must be confused. You have me confused with some other guy
So if this stage go cry me
Gosh
The thing is it's like, oh, there's one more. I see you. I see your beautiful lips
They're cute
Okay, he's I'm gonna have monogamy. He's cute, but if he says the n-word, I'm gonna ban him. Okay, better not
Come back baby come back
This stage come back, you know, you gotta hold on
Now I know he left because I said he has nice lips
See, that's why guys people like why do you hit on guys? I'm trying to get rid of them
Turning them to leave me alone. They eventually leave if I tell them I've been as butt
But then backfires half the time and they're they're interested
Yeah, you want to compare BQ to Sig? Yeah, we were being patriotic. Yeah, but she's I mean I mean she even forgave him for that
I mean it was like it wasn't like it was weird, but he was standing over her bed like drooling
I mean I'm in like doing anything really but I know it's very pretty gross, but
Thankfully she woke up and
Hell out of there
He has Tourette syndrome. Okay. Well, maybe I'll give maybe Nick I'll give him another chance on some other show
It's just not not the time right now safety
Okay
The thing is, here's the thing.
Here's what I'm willing to speak out even if it's like,
first of all, okay, oh my gosh.
You're gonna wear me out.
Okay, you left again.
I mean, stop it, stop coming up.
He has Tourette's coming on my panel, right?
No, the reason I'm speaking out right now
is because I basically don't want this to happen
to somebody again, like it happened to me.
Nice, I felt more the oaky-doke a few times
I'm not saying like you do cold make your heart cold or change or anything, but I mean well
Personally for me all my heart has gone a little bit colder and I have changed you know a little bit
But um, yeah, he's a lack of self-control. I know it's like it's a control. Yeah
He left. I mean it's tough coming up if you don't want to talk. Okay. Now you're being stupid
I'm just gonna I'm gonna actually everyone has a struggle. That's the whole thing. Is there empathy?
Or is that, and how about like the golden rule?
Even at that religious, this is like,
even atheists can have like a thing of like more thing.
I think I did it out of spite rather than being tricked
out of spite.
Like what did I do out of spite though?
I just had him, you know, in the chat and stuff.
Sage was really nice to you when he last time he came up.
He was low key.
He said worse things about me
than I said about you to your boyfriend.
I told your boyfriend that you had Down syndrome
and were in a wheelchair and 400 pounds.
What this sage has said was worse than that.
But I was confused with that.
I think their name was like Schmelly or something inside.
So I'm sorry if I got it wrong.
It's that, I remember the person that
the profile picture was like this.
Yeah.
What, Sage is not a, oh Sage was a bit,
cause he, so I don't have to keep banning his accounts.
It'll just, you know, all the stupidity of Sage will come.
It will just come.
No, you're staying off the show.
You say the facts why did you sit to you down syndrome wheelchair bound?
Loser out. Now, how do you like it? How do you like that's what she just said?
Oh, he's right when he calls me an n-word f a g g o t pdf. Okay, but
Right atheists, please. How can you not believe in either? I know what I'm just saying
I'm saying even even an atheist. I'm saying even an atheism, which I believe are I think atheists are kind of delusional because they believe in something
They believe there's not a God, right?
So they have a belief it's not it's not the absence of belief
It's a belief there's not a god the absence would be more of like a agnostic
Which is like I don't know and I'm not knowing it wouldn't be whatever
But I'm saying even an atheist gets it. You know, I think the only people that don't get it are fake people like fake Christians
people that take on the mantle of it and then like as the this is my identity, right and then
They're not. I mean, it's like, you know, I don't know
Like there's an old testament and usually the New Testament if you read the Old Testament
You'll see the God in the Old Testament is quite different from the God in the New Testament quite different
He's
very jealous, vengeful, warlike.
Oh, there's low-key again.
The first time you came in and was kind, you kicked him.
Oh, okay, there you are.
No, okay, well, then I'm sorry if I said it.
I know, oh, he wasn't kind.
He wasn't kind.
He was saying, oh, you deserve this.
You know, blah, blah, blah, blah.
No, I don't deserve it.
I don't deserve it.
I didn't do anything to deserve that, like to deserve.
And neither did other people
that aren't even involved in anything, right?
They do they deserve it so you say so so so your people think it's okay to go attack people's families
I have nothing to do is anything so great to do that
I thought I was always against that and I thought the community was too
So let's see how people are gonna like it when it happens to them
Because of its fair game if you're saying it's okay to do
It should be okay for everybody, right?
That's okay, right?
I don't have to do it, right? He's right about saying she won't stop. Okay. She'll stop
And people warn me, right, but she'll stop though.
She will stop.
I mean, she'll be stopped or she'll be made to stop legally.
What she's doing is illegal, do you understand that?
Not only on the terms of service portion of it,
but on many others and now there's ample evidence of it.
So keep providing the evidence.
His turtleneck is on too tight.
Yeah, your turtleneck is on too tight.
I got you, what?
You don't have nothing. Why are you doing this? Why are you doing? What are you? Why are you behaving this way?
Well, you're coming up and up and up and you know what not there you are you've come on nothing but kind to you
You're trying to do what unbanned all sages and glokey. I've been nothing but kind to you
No, you haven't been will you do for me if I have been it's not my fault you decide you want to be here so bad
You don't like me. Why are you predator because you're a fat?
Okay, now you're now now. I'm now I'm never I'm just gonna ban. I'm gonna ban the word. Um, whatever your other screen name
I'm gonna ban the words
Muguru
I'll unban Glocky. Okay. Okay. I mean, I'll I mean, I'll tell me every time I hold on a second
because
I missed it. Sometimes there's misunderstanding. That's why it's good to like sometimes
clarified, but you know a blog going on right now
so, uh
Why won't stop? Yeah
who won't stop? Yeah, she's saying she won't stop, right? But she will. I mean, she doesn't,
she's just doing something to herself. I mean, I don't think you understand. Like, she's doing
something to herself. And I'm not, I've asked, I've already asked her to cease and desist
on the uncertainty. And you know what, she did, but she's, but then she's, then she started using
like my, my deceased father's name and photo. How would people like that?
But how do you like would you like your deceased relative like we deceased relatives voters to be used?
And what what what what can you possibly do that would warrant that that doesn't get her fair. Oh
Sweet be hi, sweet. Thank God
Reason was a long time
It has been a long time. Oh my gosh. What did you sound like?
It's just
I know. Oh my gosh. You sound like you're like, you know, in a hospital bed or something.
I have someone who would like to speak with you.
Who is it?
His name is Arthur.
Okay, put on Arthur on the phone.
Yo, yo, yo, real quick.
Yeah. I have to start off with always. I am not here.
I do not stand for what Psyche has done, said.
I do not stand with Brendan Q. I, the test, and then you're dealing with him.
What did I do and say? What did I do and say that you have an issue with besides just having him on?
If you allow me, would you allow me to say it without you kicking me out?
Yeah, of course. What did I say? What did I say?
So, and I quote...
Just Jen was telling everyone, including you,
I think this was on your channel.
It was in the chat.
In the chat, right?
Correct.
She was in the chat.
I didn't see until after, okay?
I sometimes don't see the whole chat, okay?
I saw it after.
But you were...
And she went rogue on me, so she should be out anyways.
No, no, no, no.
This was before she went rogue on you.
She was asking you...
What?
This is what I'm saying.
Am I allowed to...
Right. Well, you're getting the facts wrong because I know what you're saying right now.
You're saying, oh, he said something terrible to her in my chat, and I didn't do anything.
I didn't see that comment. But you responded to her what she said.
If you allow me, maybe. No, I was telling him to leave her alone because they were going back
and forth. But I didn't see the specific comment where he said the thing about her son and that
was not somebody else's comment. The dogs? Well, she did fuck dogs. She did fuck dogs.
So the issue was it all stems back to when just Jen was telling you she's being very vocal about what happened
between her and Brandon Q and one of the issues was that he said to her
Hey, I know where you live and I know the the offsprings and I don't give a fuck
I'm gonna I'm gonna come after you just Jen. All right. I know that she told you. Hey, this is what happened
Please get him out. I don't feel comfortable
And you said, hey, does it matter if it's just words?
Did anything physically happen to you?
I get emotionally.
What did you say?
That's exactly what I responded to
because there was a lot being said at that time.
And so I mean, they're going back and forth
into each other about stuff.
And I thought it was maybe this really about the dogs,
not about like going-
But why would you benefit?
If you're trying to, well, what is this
when you benefit the wrong or benefit DD?
You're giving
Was my benefit that's my question. Why would you benefit the doubt to something horrible as opposed to?
Well, I don't because it wasn't an exact she didn't say Brandon started to kill me and my family
She said Brandon's being mean to me. No, she didn't say me. Nope. No. Yeah, they're just fighting with you about dogs and stuff
I saw was he said you know, I was there was nothing about dogs
She said she said she did but she said she was forced to by the by the adult industry
But she never did that she would never say that cuz you never the dogs were the victims that she had the real victims with the dogs
She didn't say that yeah
It was my daughter so again, I do not stand with what psyche has done
You know what? You know just go ahead and put a disclaimer in your name
You don't have to they don't come here if you don't like if you don't that's actually a good idea. Hey, thank you good
They don't leave. I mean, it's like whoa
So sad bye. So no, I want to call Albedo because
Then no, you know, no that psyche, right? I say every time I join here. What do I always say? I always say the same thing, right?
I always call you out and you and I go at it, right?
You just said, you're not allowed in my chat anymore
because you're on psychies and stuff like that, right?
No, no, it's worse than that.
So.
And you're a predator because you're on my show, right?
Cause you tried to smear everyone on the show, right?
So now this is the new shit with her, right?
Yeah.
She's like, oh, cause I told her, well, look,
Sammit calls in.
What's the dude that you just called in right now?
What's the black dude that you just called in, what's your name?
Damn.
The, no, no, Sage, the 39 or something.
He calls in here.
And she's like, but when they call in, they shit on him.
They don't dare to be friendly with him.
They're there to shit on him.
I'm like, well, how about you play the clip when I called in
and you can literally hear me shitting on psych
every time I jump handle.
She's like, no, you look for it.
I am not, you're the one saying that.
I'm not going to look for it.
I'm like, you're the one accusing me, I'm not doing it.
And I'm telling you, just play the clip.
I tell you, if you haven't figured out she's nuts at this point, I mean,
I mean,
I'm gonna bother with her.
She's crazy.
That's not the point for her.
Thanks.
So my point is, right?
Yeah.
Now, she gets along with Crystal Ann.
And Alexandra.
And what's his name?
No, it was actually saying, hey, why is it that you can get along and forgive her now,
even though she even took down Saman's channel, that's where he makes his money.
She said, then what did she say?
That's that's none of my business. I only I am cordial with her
I don't I don't like what she did, but that doesn't mean I have to shit on her so wait
So why do I have to shit on psych every time?
But you can get along with uh, what's her face now chrysaline? She's always telling me
She's while I hear that clip I did hear the chrysaline just now she was like look I heard you calling in
Why don't you not shit on him? You know he did a lot to send man
He does a lot of a lot of bad things to send man, but then chrysaline take down
Samans way of making money
Yeah, but she also is about to put it back up because it'll piss everybody off, she said, but yeah.
Now she's going to be like, you know, but it's just, you know, Crystal Anne is not the same.
Maybe that's why, you know, that's why she likes her now is because, you know, it's like, you know,
you know, now she can get her to take the strikes down and she's nice to her, do a little diplomacy
because she's like an Iranian fucking ambassador, right?
Anyway, Bita's a two-phase. We all know that.
She is very fake. She is very fake.
Everyone agrees with that.
Yes. I hope everyone here in the chat can...
Everyone does. Everyone does.
Realize that.
I got you now, Arthur.
Okay, Arthur, you're in trouble now.
Whoa, whoa, wait. Did she say that?
Yeah.
Oh, wow. See, there you go.
The threats. The threats.
Hey, you deserve all your karma, too, Bita, and, you know...
Oh, good things happen to you too, right?
Well, there you go. She's threatening me, but then I-
It only just begun. It has only begun.
How do you know? Are you God, bitch?
You understand my karma?
You understand my having unfair things done to you
and illegal things done to you and the innocent people?
That's bad karma.
Their karma has only begun, bitch.
Hey, say-
No, karma works.
Hey, Chad, did I wish any threats,
any harm on being a right now?
Why is she saying all this to me?
What justifies is saying all that
Why why is she's saying all these things right she's threatened big phone a bitch
I'd appreciate her more if she could just be like, you know what I'll do whatever the fuck I want and you can do
Whatever the fuck you want. No, no, no, no, she has to be in control of other people and she has to say
Because you have bullied in high school and she was like the weird Iranian girl with acting a big nose
I feel bad
Oh, it's only just because I'm calling her a fake bitch, but I won't go all.
No, it's a fake beta.
I won't speak.
Yo, damn, that shit got a fat ass.
God damn fake beta.
Yeah.
Well, I won't call beat all that.
I just she's very fake.
She's the phony.
I can't stand it.
You know, like stop judging me, beta.
De Soto said, De Soto said, big judge.
De Soto said, beta is 60 and she says meow out and she's sad.
I know that's for you.
I really have no beef with her, but it's just it's just annoying when a lot of the fakes shit with her
That's it. I don't wish any harm to you. Let me call it out right now
I do not wish any harm on you
Nothing at all. Christine says I'm I look like I'm 85 years old or something like that
I don't think I look 85 years old. I think I look okay, but it's just 84
Years old. I mean, it's yeah, it's not 85. I was well look when I'm 84
Well, like over a hundred. I mean this thing that's like I thought I had better genetics than that
I mean, you might be insulting and fine Arthur. I just know you're full of shit. It's called a joke. Come on. Just relax
Jokes usually are followed by laughter
There's no one else here to laugh. I'm not gonna laugh at my own joke and you're not gonna laugh
Hands I didn't laugh and none other than any of the chat. Oh, there's big bonkers nose job has nothing to talk about
Oh big bonkers. I'm all mine. Good. Do you mean big beaker or you have big bonkers?
What you blank had a nose job because your nose was I told everyone I had a nose job
I know I had a nose job, but it's probably so did you and thank God come on
But I'm not gonna make fun of you. I know you're one and she's running a smoke with me. Okay. Hey, you know what I get it
Yeah, the nose nose as I'm very nose nose. Yes, the nose nose people and Johnny's skin
Deputy or whatever. No, you're just this stage or something go away. I do not be the
I had a nose job I did I when I said in tea because I was like betas and I had to have a fix I mean jeez
Well, I
Again, I'm gonna say this even though she's threatened the shit out of me right now
I know you want him back on her show, beat his leg man.
Let him on the fucking show.
I mean, you're like everybody-
I'm banned.
I'm banned over there, dude.
Pathetic.
She's just pathetic.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's like-
She'll ban me, but she'll ban me,
but she won't ban others that fucking-
Oh, I get banned in Sandman's chat.
I'm not allowed in her fan.
I mean, it's like, I'm not allowed in so many places
because she's like, oh, he's telling you.
Oh my God.
And then she has Christine even fighting
with Summer over her.
Like, you know, you know,
because you're forcing Christine to take sides and stuff,
right?
I think that's part of it. Yeah, I think I think what happened I think you're kind of touching the water
I think you're getting it wrong. You're saying I'm dipping my toe into the water on an idea here
Yes, yes, but you're you're diving into the wrong side of the pool right now. Let me take you to the right side
So this is what I think again, I think I'm not saying this is what happened Christine
Is it gonna be like you're spratting fake news? This is just my opinion
Okay, Christine. I don't wish any harm on you or your family as a matter of fact
I hope you have a happy retirement whenever that day comes Christine. It's the summertime
I think you're a sweet old lady. I have no issue with you. This is just my opinion
think that probably summer got a little bothered that Christine was no longer
you know on that side of the hemisphere she decided to go to the Iraqi or the
Iranian side and you know probably she got a little jealous you know women
could be a little hostile or what is this when they when they think something is
theirs possessive yes
I think Summer is very possessive.
She has a very strong attitude, personality,
and she probably got a little jealous.
You know what it is.
You know, Bita gets more views over there
as opposed to Summer.
Summer gets, like, max 22 views.
Who cares?
I mean, is this really a view contest?
I mean, it doesn't really matter.
I think that's what...
I think that's what she...
Yeah, I mean that's a very superficial kind of thing to worry that's pretty worried about that, right? Oh, I mean like it's summer. She's very superficial
Well, I mean summer does have a cause behind her like, you know, she has like the charity thing
And so it's like even she doesn't want to build her charity and would like to have more attention to the outreach
And I would I would say to go donate to summer to and support her outreach and she was great work
And she's out there on camera doing it all and she was anyway
I'm sorry. I like you got hurt and I banned you, you know the reason why but please have some self-awareness and say the fuck
Uh, stay away from this fucking freaking nature.
I'm a fucking freak of nature, Bita.
I'm a fucking freak of nature.
Okay, you know how big your...
Bita, your bush is an area code and zip code, okay?
Your bush, basically gardeners get lost in your vagina, okay?
Oh, you cur...
So she does curses.
Oh, that's pretty curseable, right?
Okay. Yeah. Well, here's your Persian curse
You know, be there did save the day with with a Michael one day because she did a reading from hafiz and she gave him all this advice
And it said you have she she's like if you don't do this you're gonna die and he died
And so, you know, I think be to kill them. Oh, come on. What?
Let's just stop talking about me. No, that's what I have it on video where she does that
She's yeah, but that's not good. I don't know. Yeah, you can either follow what I'm gonna say right now
Or you or you'll die, right? And oh my goodness. Come on. That's what seriously. That's what she said. Yes. Yes
But we already know what happened then there's nothing related to her
Right, but I'm going to metaphysical, right?
No, come on. He I look I'm gonna put this out
He passed away, ladies and gentlemen.
I don't think we should be speaking about him.
He's being bullied by Bita and Tracy online.
Oh my God. I'm not the team name, dude.
I'm not allowed to mention it. Don't mention the team name.
I'm allowed to say it, but yeah, you can't.
I'm here for you. Oh, she's lab. I'm a scared beta
Because you actually didn't you lose a channel beta and you're so you're actually vanivating, you know, YouTube took away your channel
Question the same as channel get taken down for good or he's just on like a day a couple weeks notice
Well, he's on Air Force Sam, but I'm Chris I'm Chris lands about to take him back up. Yeah
Also, he never really got the lead in.
Yeah, it's not, I think the other one has strikes on it,
but if she takes the strikes down, they'll be back, you know?
Go report it, Bita, go get your little report,
but I think he's the only one I've ever reported.
Oh, and it's like everybody, I mean,
RG has fucking show with, you know,
her calling her, you know, you know,
Anthony Raun on the show and stuff,
and she doesn't even care.
But it's like, I say one thing,
I'm gonna report you, sit there with your paperwork
and your fucking thing.
I mean, geez, Bita, come on,
a little bit pathetic at this point, okay?
Thank God.
Yo, the women out here looking fine as hell, dude, God dang.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
So Arthur, you're straight, Arthur, I didn't even know that.
What?
Are you kidding me?
Come on, dude.
So all right, look, I'm going to put an ultimatum to you
and hear me out, hear me out before you start crashing out.
I don't take ultimatum, so don't even make it.
I get it, I get it, but just hear me out.
There is this community I go to, right?
And he was like, yo.
He was saying, yo, man, I'm, you know, I'm really like the stream yard shit, man.
I really wish I could connect with more communities, more, more streamers out there.
And I gave him some names.
I'm like, yo, oh, shit, yo, I mean, and you seem like a pretty cool dude.
As far as I know, I started to give him names.
I'm like, yo, there's this, this channel.
There's this channel.
And I was like, damn, I don't know if Samus channel is still alive.
I gave him Samus channel.
And then I thought about giving them your channel, but you didn't.
Because of this situation, but you might in the future if I if I considered your advice right now
Go ahead your view of your advice if if you can just stay away from the whole queue branding
Yes, he's banned from the show Arthur. He's banned from the show. He's never coming home. I promise you. It's a promise
As I swear to God. On my own on my own authority and my own reputation. I promise I'll not have Brandon back
There you go. Oh shit. You heard it here ladies and gentlemen. He's gone so
He's gonzo. He's he's he's he's go back to his own terrible show. Okay, you can watch we'll go watch him play
You know fortnight or something like that and bitch about Ganville if you want to go see very nice you
You know, what's that?
What's that clip or that command there? He's like ladies and gentlemen
We got him. Yeah, you know when they were talking about saying Obama or some shit
That was oh, so some bin Laden right Osama bin Laden. That's right. Some but some attorney or somebody was like ladies and gentlemen
It might have been the same, but no, it was the same as something like that.
Like Barack Hussein Obama, something like that.
Yeah.
Saki many other people would be you know, I haven't had he's been banned for quite a while though
I mean, it's like you know, he's been banned for like a you know over a week and so I guess that just takes time for the word to get out
But yeah, I mean if you can spread the word, but it's like that again
It's like I'm not I'm never to be forgiven for anything. I'm nothing's ever
I mean everything for me is like no all the rules apply even the rules that aren't rules
They're just made up, but everybody else can get away with it for given and of course I'll forgive them
but it's like
People are just so unforgiving towards me. I understand
Because I mean, let me explain like, you know, I mean or how about like if you're my friend you can like
Because you're like you came up and talked to me even if you like you really disagree and stuff
I mean, I was I would listen to you because I like you and stuff
And I say at least listen to your
Opinion and input and then we're coming from a pretty genuine place as opposed to like Tony trying to tell me what to do
And it's like he's by the same time sending me many mansons vagina pictures and oh my wait. Hold on
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. It's mini man's in a chick. We're a do-it-what is he?
Born a biological female, but she is or he is now a male and that is his that is his
Okay, so he has a pussy. Yeah, he has a pussy, but he wants a dick
Well, that's it. Well, you know, it's kind of like
Incentive a pussy man hat
He can't have that because unless he like you know buys went to store because basically they don't they don't have the surgery
That good enough to give that to
So women yet or so you could never really be a trans man
You're gonna be a trans woman
Yeah, you can be like pretty much everything like the hormones will change everything to a man
And they'll even like make the clip like really really swollen and stuff. So it's almost like oh my god
It's like a hot dog bug more than a penis
But still it's good enough
You can actually like you can put on strap on those these old studs
Which are bloody black lesbians that are really like masculine and they were like a strap on like at all times
Even at the urinal and stuff like it's like and which is like a trick
I don't know how they do that, but yeah, I mean many Manson looks fucking satanic a shit, dude
Well, it's you know many man like many Manson is based on kind of like Marilyn Manson and also Satanism and stuff and so
She is that does that thing still calling over here?
Don't cut VVV for like to say she
Many all right, I'm just calling me. Yeah, yeah, mini. Yeah, mini was just in the show recently
What we had a good show with mini recently. Oh, man
I remember that one time. I think it was a couple of streams ago a couple months ago. Sorry
He she be they them he he was fucking a crash and I remember they just started to say the n-word
Yeah, it was because I like gaudi on at the same time they were on and they got mad and then they started like, you know
But you know they
Many man's didn't like moon to Lisa on Lisa's stream. Oh, thank you. Why? Yeah, we say transgender
Yeah person in church. Hi. Yeah
Hey, anybody that, like, I mean, I will not only leave Vita's name out of my mouth,
I'll ban her name from my chat. How about the fuck that?
Oh, shit. Nah, come on. We still need...
You guys are like Batman and Joker. You guys need one or another.
You can spell her name with the real spelling. Thank you.
It was a great show. Thank you so much.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Tell me one thing you don't like about beta like what is the biggest thing you don't like about I don't like about beta
Because I was on the show with you. I think it was like I remember exactly
I remember I was like May of last year April or May
Yeah, you said you she said uncle effort and what I do or I kicked you right off the show didn't I yes you did yeah
Well, I cannot and she still brings it up. I could never live it down. It's my fault. He said it
I mean, it's like she's still mad about that. I mean, she's forgiven you and everyone else
But it's like I
because you were on the show at the time and said it,
and I even thought if it kicks you off,
it's my fault, right?
So that's probably one of the biggest things
you don't like about her, right?
Well, that she's like so...
Just one thing, just one thing for now.
I think that's one thing, right? All right.
Now can you give me one thing you do like about her?
Well, I think there's probably a good side to her,
but I don't see it anymore, so I don't like it.
How about maybe she really takes care of her cats?
Um, you could tell she's an eca woman
I would always defend her with her cats and stuff like that until she now she's starting to go after mine and stuff
And so I'll say
her cats are kind of gay.
I mean, it's like, you know,
they're a little bit toddled.
They're like homeschooled.
And I mean, as I believe cats should be let outside,
but it's like, you know,
we have different opinions
and raise our kids, raise our cats is different.
You know, I don't feed my cats the coyotes.
It's just like the cats are outdoor cats.
There happened to be occasional coyote.
And it's like, so there is a like, you know,
a small danger of that,
but it's, can I go out and like, like
I mean, I'm trying to-
Of course.
No, it's like, I love my fucking cats.
My cats are my baby and stuff.
And so it's like, you know,
and then to constantly call me animal abuser.
I'm starving them, they're sick.
And they're the happiest fucking huge cats in the world.
I mean, it's like-
Raw, raw.
I think at the end of the day,
you two need to talk it out.
Just the two of you on screen. Oh, no chat a hundred thousand. Yeah, but no chat. No chat. No
He's he needs bodyguard. He's yeah, no Christine
None of the other Christine. What's the what's the what's her name chicken cow or something cow? Yeah
Chicken cow like none of the Christine's on panel. We don't know none of the same as nothing nothing
No chat just until you streaming
and just hash it out.
Okay, so Casey says,
some cats don't go outside, Saki.
You know, are cats naturally born indoors
and in a hospital bed?
You know, cats come from the African wild cat.
All cats do, you know.
So they are wild and something.
They like to, you know,
they're not gonna like lose the love of like,
you know, eating a bird or a mouse and stuff like that.
Right?
Yes, I am the Hispanic doctor, Phil.
Yeah, that's why they got nails.
Yeah.
Kitty gang for life unbanals. Oh, it's that oh my gosh. Can you get it? Can you get it?
Can you know I changed the name of the kitty gate? I have a fk fk fpkg. I believe that's the new logo
I do want to throw this out there as well. I do wave the same in flag. Oh
My god, we get proud Lee. Well your Arthur get out of your bikini
And the dick out from between your legs and be a man
Samenz doesn't want your glazing.
Even he's disgusted by you.
I mean, he's like-
I'm not-
I'm not a bitch.
Even he says that to you.
But I'm not trying to do that for him.
I'm just-
I know, but it goes off bad, Arthur.
It just looks even stupider than I did with the Brandon Q situation when you lick his
butt hole.
No.
That situation's-
I saw you get kicked off of Sam Anstall and he's like, five, four, three, and you know
No.
that, you know, the horrible Boston Bridgette, you know, author, author, and then she goes
somewhere with you.
Don't, I don't, you don't not want to talk about her, no, I didn't say that.
You're gonna make yourself a whole new enemy dude. I don't even care. She's already my enemy
Yeah, dude, she is like a fucking like a termite in your nuts, bro
She will not leave you alone. You're done, dude. Sam is gonna send her that clip now. Well good. I don't care
He is for her pounds. I've seen her. I've seen her. Yeah
Disgusting and she's like pretty cool, man. You gotta give her
What was wrong with sucking a dick every day?
Well, there's something wrong with it.
You don't want to stuff too many of them.
They might have a serious disease or something.
I don't know.
Jeez.
Come on.
Stop talking about sucking.
I'm not bossing, man.
I'm just eating a hot dog.
I mean, come on.
Get a light.
Boston's the sweetheart, dude.
Come on.
She looks like a Boston cream pie.
Oh, because you want to fill her up?
Oh, and it's smashing her face.
Oh, my goodness.
Come on, oh, my goodness.
All right.
There's no way you're coming back, so.
Boston, you know, BB that was not me. That was all him because I'm on my mom panel with him. It does not mean I
I agree with what he says or does.
Right, and Volga, I don't agree with going in real life
on anybody.
If you have a problem, just talk to them on a panel
or say something, you don't have to like,
oh, dog scene, it's like the dog scene is so stupid
and it's like, you know, because like for like,
you know, Les started doing it and he got bitten in it
and now he's like crying.
I mean, it's like, you know, just like leave people out
of it.
I mean, how about like fight a fight?
How about like, first of all, pick up someone
your own size.
Like, I'm like, you know, I'm just a little channel.
I'm,
I'm just little like this little little lip in the air, and then there's big
Like they're so they're so insecure about me even getting oh his viewers
I'm gonna go in and like you destroy him
I'm more popular
And it's like it's like, okay. Well, what are you do your ancient Rome or something like that?
You're some bitch and you're a bitch to zoo gang and you know zoo gang that means you're a zoo file and so you fuck the animals
Oh
Shout out to sweet people ever she's that
Thanks doctor
She's in my house.
What are your thoughts on Crystal Anne?
We're the Giants, I mean, they're not Giants,
but they're fat, Vita and Samman.
They're not Giants, but they're pretty fat.
Not the fat people.
She is a little ugly, right?
Yeah.
Inside Anne, though.
I was watching her stream earlier today.
My goodness, she is boring.
I mean, it's like, it's hard to do a show and stuff.
I mean, she has to kind of like, you know,
I mean, I don't want to, I want to be like,
I mean, it's like-
The issue is like when she's reading the chat,
like she's quiet.
What you're supposed to do is probably read it out loud and then interact with it well
You know the problem is she doesn't have you up there on panel to make it interesting Arthur and so it's like that's
She's missing out. It's a bad business move
I'm through with the same man flag brother. I know and it's a rainbow flag right with the Puerto Rican little thing on the corner
It's okay, it's a Arthur. We can you can you ride my float at the parade go house on a Perry what?
In the parade, we're gonna wear Speedos and do volleyball on the float.
Wait, how do you know about that?
I know everything.
Hey, hey, what's up INX, how are you, sweetheart?
DeSoto, sweetie's probably McDonald's, yeah.
Oh, is she here?
No, go, INX is, yeah.
Because I heard a...
Great her crystal and her is her daughter. She's like I annex 2.0. Is that true daughter is Crystal Anne's daughter is over
It's like three rubber dolls, but no, no, no, she's not related to I know I'm saying I had nexus
No, I don't know sorry Chris Lane is I had nothing done is that I next are you Chris to land's mother? I didn't know that
I don't think she is, I don't think she is.
I'm pretty sure she is.
I think she's like a fucking blob per se.
Yeah, like Kate had a, I think Kate got my idea
cause like I made a six dig of blob fish
and then like Crystal Anne was a blob fish last night.
So we're all going to have blob fish
for like fucking dinner this month.
Happy, happy, happy July.
How was your July 4th, Arthur?
Well, it was, it was all right.
Just stayed home, nothing special.
Yo, I'm going to go right inside real quick.
I need to get myself something to eat.
I'll be right back.
Okay
And stream do not end stream, dude. I won't you come join me in the pool afterward. Okay. I mean
Those bubbles on so you won't be able to see you. Thank you. Oh, okay. Bye Arthur
No, Arthur was once a amateur wrestler and
Yeah, we hop
Okay, so I just want to do something real quick. Yeah, I don't know
I don't know. I just get a, you know, everyone will, like, basically, you know, I don't want to, like, be baited into reactions and stuff, but at the same time, I'm trying not to be baited into the reaction, I'm trying to, hopefully...
prevent another tragedy from happening to somebody else because look at look at poor me look at look at me look at me
What happens to me? I think you try to be nice
You try to you bring love and stuff like that and it's like you know
You're just trampled over shit on and and slandered us up
And you know what the bad guy wins sometimes, but ultimately I don't think they always will win
I think I think ultimately they lose, you know, I don't think that
Doing bad to others
Will reap an ultimate positive reward it might do some good stuff in the short term just like robbing a bank
That'll do good for your money in a short term, but then you've robbed a bank
And so you have all this other so the money's not good and the button the fucking you know
There's your own surveillance camera and all this kind of shit, right? So there's a lot of other stuff going on
This one right here
Um, yeah, she doesn't kind of look like a blob bitch, but fuck her slam
I mean, I'm really like so many of the people here just burn me so bad that it's like I'm just so thankful that I do have a few
Real ones and it's like, you know, I know thank you for people to say bye. You're brave because it's like wow
It's like all the fucking shit. I mean and they should I have to go through and say, you know, sometimes people, you know
Get the strap little and I know people get you know, they want to hear that fun, but I promise you
If you like have my back, I will have your back and you know.
I look out for my friends.
I don't start shit with people.
I don't go out looking for fights.
They're started with me over a million things.
And it's like, and so then I'll sometimes react
because I can have a sharp tongue.
I have an inner protector that like,
doesn't like to see me get bullied and used
and slandered and called things
and spoken out of my name.
And also like to have ancestors that care about my family
and don't like some of the bullshit they go on.
Even some of other people's families
in the spirit realm are interested in this situation.
and are very concerned. I'll just put it that way. But I'll be right back.
Silence yourself, drink to fit, no disguise, no more filled
dirt.
Lins into chest and calls it love I should have guessed.
I said he's coming, so I'll do one more thing, one more segment.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Can we watch the beat?
I would love to watch that, I mean, we can, but I'm, I don't know if it is the right day
to do it.
But you know, the thing is with, I'll tell J-Dog about it, there we go.
I'll tell J-Dog what happened.
Plan was and whatever I didn't I mean it's like I mean I should have seen things like I should have seen that
I saw that she didn't like like white
People I mean I should have just realized she and gay people shouldn't like I mean the whole thing was
Yeah, just read last night. It's like she
This guy was like he's gay. She's like this woman been attacking me for years for being gay and stuff
She's like a homophobe
So I didn't know about that side of her
So that's very dangerous when you let when you let like people that actually hate who you are
genetically or you know intrinsically they hate you I mean it's like and then
sometimes those people are like you know sometimes not loved very much and
are thirsty for love and maybe I was a little bit I was a little thirsty bitch
maybe who knows but uh you know now I have water poisoning
You can't get rid of me Arthur W. He's being evil
Let them talk to talk to him sweepy. Oh my god
Hey, psyche, what's up, dude? How you doing?
No, I'm just chilling bro chilling, you know, I saw that video. I saw the dope
Do an entire virtual tour of your parents?
You don't have to say J-Doc because that's all in the legal stuff, but I'm gonna say okay. Okay. My bad my bad
Say like yeah, it's like on way too far and it's like I didn't do anything to this one
I didn't I didn't I was literally like a week ago
You know even the day that she decided to like turn on me
She said me this tripod, you know, I didn't ask for the time
Which is I'm sending you something I walked up the door was like right at the doorstep like in that day
But that was like, she's like, that was a parting gift.
So maybe there was something behind it.
But, you know what, RG has been up here almost every day since this incident, saying, just
go in the chat and say, oh, no, it's your chat dad, you deserve this, blah, blah, and
he's like, but he's friends with her, and on her panels, she did the same thing.
She blames the feature of the brand and the Q stuff.
She says, oh, well, you know, you brought me into this, but she brought me into it really,
because I was done with this topic, and she decided to like have this whole like redemption
tour, and I was stupid enough to go up there and be part of it.
ever again like dude i saw that that video was like good hello early this morning i was like
what the fuck i was like oh wow good like hella doc scene hello i know it's totally illegal it's
completely illegal and it's like you know i don't even do the rent and then talking about the rent
like like oh okay i'm sorry my bad my bad
It's just like it's like it's basically just very illegal stuff going on. You don't you don't you don't want to touch it with a 10 foot pull anybody
Okay, yeah, yeah, I don't want to get a step on toes or nothing, but
Let's just like I'll say is like, you know, there's there's a point if you have a problem with somebody you can go after them
You can say whatever you want to them you can have a relationship. I mean all this stuff where it goes
RL and especially when assisting such as lame is like having pizzas delivered or you know annoying people and stuff
What video of Sam and be that that was the I next video where you they have their camera slips and be that has like
She's like bald and then he's like
I was just tripping out. I saw that video. I was like, oh psyche's gonna
But you know what? The whole point of those things is like to scare, to intimidate.
But there are things called laws in the country, where beyond even like YouTube terms of service,
which these things are very much against, and you know,
you got banned from YouTube for doing these things, right?
You know, you can't, you're not supposed to do certain things.
These are very, very, very illegal things.
Because they get into even more like liability for YouTube
with these things that can happen outside of it.
And so, it gets crazy.
But, yeah, and then she's saying that I'm not gay
because I didn't meet with you that weekend, right?
And I met with her, so I must have been straight,
even though, you know.
I don't know, it was like, I just like to meet people, but it's like, I don't know if it wasn't like, I wasn't intentionally trying not to meet you or something like that, it was just kind of like, you know.
No, just bad timing, that's all it was. You know, it's what happens, shit happens.
That's like, what kind of thing, now I'm being called, yeah, beat is even saying I'm straight, because I'm so, I'm so, I'm so, I'm so dirty, I couldn't be gay, because gay people are clean and...
Dude, that's a backstabbing old type.
You guys are like little like oh be that like that. I mean how I kind of like maybe it was more when she met me
I was like a little bit more
Honestly bro, I'm gonna tell you this in the beginning when you beat up first Matt
You came off more straight
I did you did because you came off you came off like
You were flamboyant, but not as flamboyant like now you're just like now you're just like I don't give a fuck
I am who I am like that my parents are straight
You know and so it's like we're straight people, you know two straight people got together at a street
But but sometimes a gay man and a woman can have a baby too. Show it for those that miss it
Have you seen that that video?
J-Dog or yeah, there's also a spectrum too. If you've seen the video I and X about beta and Sam and I
No, I have not
I don't know if it's still up. I can't check if it's still up
It's a short video. It's just like you just see like
These judgmental people and stuff like that who are always they say oh show us your floor show us your this show us your that
And then he's talking about feeding his fish and he has an empty fish tank
There's there's no live fish in there and the fish have died months ago in that thing
How dare you dude and and these days who even has a fish tank do fish tanks are so 80s and 90s bro
I don't even know
These computers on a folding picnic table or something like that
So little rubber-made ones as long as you get a Walmart
So here's the this is the real faces
So this is pretty good though
I don't know that is backstage. Let me check those two. Okay. Hold on to the yeah
There you go
Oh, yeah, that's being a spoke in a pack of men's phones. What is it?
But beta you won't show your face that's why you hide in the background in the dark
Close to your back window
And you won't show your face at all, but you're way back there in the dark
But then when you show your cats you put the lights on this is beat up with the bald head
She's got a bald spot on the top of her head, and that's why you see her put her hair
over her face and she has skin tags and a crater face and
Crystal was the one that exposed that about the crater face
And this is Bita's face with the crater face.
You see that she's got, she won't show her face
and she's got skin tags and stuff around her eyes.
And this picture, this came on by accident
when she was screaming at Q.
So they're using her pictures again and she's upset.
But this is Bita and she can't change her face.
People have seen what I look like
and have lost over a hundred pounds by 2018.
I was always thin when I was a kid too.
At that time that I'd gotten fat and it was only for like two and a half years and people have seen me
But look at this ugly mug
She can't change this and then she had the nerve to say another streamer has a big nose when her nose is just as big
And this is Samuel. This is his recent picture. He won't go face and he has the nerve to tell other streamers you show face and I'll show face and beta said that too.
To crystal Marie who even went on Cameron shoulder face and beta still didn't show her face. This is salmon now that's an empty fish tank in the back.
And the air mattress is below that. It's air mattress
Halsey look at how ugly he is and unkept. Look, that's him now. He has no job
He has a criminal background. He was in prison when he was 16 and yes, he did get great
That's on there a salmon. Everybody knows the truth about you
PDF
These games with these kids and you were caught a few times in there hitting on kids, but this is him
Show face because I have show face salmon because this is what you look like now and this is him now
And this was um KK had showed all this because they used to FaceTime see this is how he looks now look at him
He does a lot of lean he killed his dog. I don't know if he didn't I don't think he did it on purpose
but his dog was was
Drinking the lean the bowl that he put down and that's how the dog died your careless your drug
You have no job. You're on the internet all day 24 hours wearing that wearing that dingy
uh
T-shirt that you have now
uh guys i have the video that i uh shared uh from that live and it was barry
um
So i don't know this person i'm gonna let them up on the stage alone
I might be watching them brand thank you
Hello cut you
Oh, please
I cut you off. No, I kicked you off my show Brandon. I kicked you off my show
You didn't kick me out. I mean, it's like maybe you kicked me up here
So I don't I don't go there your show. But yeah, I definitely kicked you off my show you cut me off
You're still here bitch. Geez
Still coming up on the pan. I mean geez, you know, how do we not know that that was him? How did that was like such a easy
Like guess dude, he's talking, you know
Wow, you get in line, but hopefully I mean
It all started kind of a sweepy if you really think about it cuz sweet people the first one making videos of you those shorty clips
I'll no longer be making videos about you when I am very much first in the show. I was like, oh god. Thank god
She didn't care on she gives I think you know her one channel when I'm a second PhD PhD
Which is like a haters club channel. Yeah, I'm still being posted there. Oh my
I think I stole and stuff and it's like obviously I didn't but they take it all I think
Yeah, he didn't maybe an accident
Well, I mean it's like you know what
It's like there's two people there's usually you know evidence to record what she says
I mean, it's like, you know, that's what I think people level lie a lot
But then it's like when you actually have receipts and stuff like that
Oh, there she is in the chat
Get out out I'm gonna shout out out. She really is there
Oh my god, bro
I know but you all said the same thing about LD and they say the same thing about like a lot of people that until I'm always like
I mean
I really don't care who's on the show because it's not like you can like reach out in the TV and like grab somebody unless you're like
Fucking doing legal shit, which is like, you know, I mean you're not supposed to you take this into like that's supposed to like go
Stop a celebrity in your life
You ever hear about people that like go try to meet Michelle Piper and go to her house and stuff like that and oh do they rob
Her clothes when she's not home on vacation
Yeah
you know, it's illegal. I mean, it's like these stalkers, it's considered stalking,
stalking, you know, it's like crazy behavior. Am I out? You know.
walking to people's houses and stuff, no.
I mean, jeez.
Everyone says, oh, he's a stalker because of what?
Because I put Christine's, you know,
jumping off a bridge in a meme,
if it's Sweepee is like a 600 pound woman.
I don't even know what these people really look like.
Her pictures, yeah.
Well, Sweepee did put up a picture
and the picture that she did put up
was like from like 2008, 2009.
She tried to say that that picture was like from 2020,
like 21 or 22 from 2020.
I'm like there's no way those clothes and that's her name and everything she's like basically and like right during high school and it's like
Yeah, yeah, Jim you better watch yourself you better not but if she still looks like that me till now like
Like just show show show what they really look like like why is everybody so scared of like look at us
Well, me and you are on camera. We don't care about being
essential about how we look and what yeah
Everything we show I've shown everything they want to point out our flaws and and our get our our downfalls and they say oh
the little rafters, you know, the little like, you know, oh, here, we're like, we're safe back
here, like it's easy where you're under a bridge or a troll's under a bridge and there's people
like walking top of the bridge and there's stuff going on top of the bridge and you're seeing
It's like and you look like trolls. I mean they look like literal trolls, too
I mean it's like really I wish people looked more like their hearts
Why would you go on camera when there's a stalker's like your own?
Well, I think they know what I look like at this point, right bitch
I mean, it's like really I think they know I mean I've already been on camera for thousands and thousands of hours
You literally remember a picture I posted a year ago. Well, I don't know
We'll take your post get a year
Yeah, what what stalkers like you around jazz not stalker. You're a soccer. Yeah, I hear you got socks
Yeah, no, I oh, yeah next in Guthrie's free freeing and clear. Yeah. Yeah, she's alive and well
No, dude, I remember her picture that she posted a year ago. I do because that was like the only real picture
we got of Sweet Pea. It's kind of like Victoria on her shadow. She only
saw this her shadow so that's all we can go off of. She's like a stick figure
but here's my theory. What if Victoria is not even a girl? What if Victoria is
trans? It could be trans. That's why they don't want to go on camera.
And I like Victoria. She's funny. I like her voice and I like her like her mom
stick to the dynamic with her mom and the house and stuff and and she's nice to me.
She's been nice to me so I have no problem with her um yeah rent okay I'll
rent you I'll rent you Arthur but you have to remember
Oh, dude in that awful boss can bring it bro. Oh
Do she do it it's like
It's not it's a kind of an annoying access not even a one that you wanted here
And she tries to give her funny voice is like
Like if she fuck it like if she wouldn't got a balloon and suck all the helium out of them
And tries to give little funny voices to make everybody laugh. It's like
Dude, that's how Christian sounds bro, because she smoked like 50 cigarettes a day probably got a little hole in her throat
Football of nicotine
Carbina car Carson the James
It's like, yeah.
So, guys, as mean as I get right now,
as mean as it sounds,
I'm just talking on myself, not inciting.
Go, you know, leave this person to show.
I'm not saying go to this person.
I'm not doxy or anything.
I'm just like sitting here,
maybe saying some like fucking shit,
but do you see the shit that's being said about me all day?
And so I'm a little bit sassy.
Yeah, let me at least that's the gay part of me. I'm a little bit sassy sometimes. Let me have at least that I'm not
sense, and I'm not like, you know
The tag tag is the light
What how would you what type of gay would you consider yourself flaky if you would you know how they have like like
Bear what is it like they have the bears?
I
What are the other ones they have? I don't know all the pretty
pretty skinny bear with no hair, you know?
Okay.
No, I'm not really, I'm not a bear.
I'm not any of that.
See, the thing is I don't really fit into the gay community.
I'm like, maybe like, I'm kind of like skinny,
but it's like, I thought I'm not like,
and I'm a little bit flamboyant.
I'm like, I'm like, I'm just on a spectrum,
just like, you know, with autism.
I'm somewhere on this, on this big, this big line.
I don't know where.
It's hard to judge because I'm, I just am who I am, you know?
I'm not.
Oh, no, I didn't say I just act normally, but maybe there are people do kind of learn sometimes
Who kicked the football? I don't know who kicked the football bad time to stream. Oh, yeah, so Jay
Yeah, so yeah, that was accurate. Thank you so much. I know I like I like Jim Jay. I knew I liked like them
Who kicked the football? I don't know you'd life kick the football
And what was that on South Park, he's like
Um.
You know, Bita's just gotten so unbearable, like she's just gotten so, like, it was like,
I think it's like, when she like teamed up with Samman, she's like.
Between us we have two hundred people in our chat. We are
This shit they think they're just like, oh, that's the even if the two cares about
Everyone's real everyone's talking. It's just like, hey, well, you know people are you know the chance moving at least
You know, it's like I think dude
They're the bully they're the truth
They get they supposedly they get the most viewers, but they're the ones who never came up
Right.
As Kevin doesn't do any content, he just clips shows.
And since they're playing controls, make-up streams,
Bita sits there, you know, like, you know,
crying on white claws.
And then people just go to see the cast.
I mean, people watch for different reasons.
But I want to have people start watching.
Dude, that was so crazy, the way she just randomly just
jumped on your stream all drunk that night.
And it caused, like, such a ruckus
that even caused emotional distress to your neighbors.
Because it woke them up and bothered them.
Her voice is so loud.
I mean, I can't hear my voice.
Like, my voice, I scream like this all day.
Like, it was her.
It was like this little thing.
They're like, oh my god, it looks like there's a woman
screaming inside there.
Make sure she's OK.
I mean, it's like, wow.
It's like, she sounds like some kind of drunk animal.
Oh, did you hear what had happened?
One of her parents passed away. Oh
Yeah, so she she is confiding now
In bed, but yeah, she's combined with beta, but you know she went to Q first and well Q fucked her over
He said he didn't give a shit it. Well, he he don't like you. You know how Q is he don't give a fuck about nobody
But it's also the thing is she wasn't she's attracted to a minute that kind of broke her heart
She was waiting to like kind of like have a little well. Yeah, she paid his car insurance too for the for the like a month or something
Yeah
Well, how I mean, I can talk about it shows about me and then I'm not allowed on her show to defend myself
No, no, dude. She's as bad as beta. She's they're real quick to talk about everybody, but then
Yeah, and then kick them off it. Well, why would you kick the content? Why would you cut the content that makes no sense?
They're just silly silly people
I know you but look looky. I know but I'm not telling you don't go to beat is beat is telling people don't go to here
She's even telling people that are my chat. Oh, you're a predator protector because you're in this chat
They call it goes to pedophile inside. I mean
She called ghost a pedophile. Yeah, what what it goes. What am I doing? He didn't know brand new brand if you was you like what?
So I think what we need to do bro is we got to give your channel a good cleansing of Brandon Q
You got to eliminate that little fucking weasel out of your fucking aura
Do I say to people don't go here don't go there or I'm gonna call you and start slandering you on my show
No, I let people go wherever they want and so it's them
That have the problem with that and then them that have me blocked not me and are they blocked here?
No, they can come defend themselves. You want to know it's crazy. Good. I this is like fucking deja vu. I swear to God
I get this with another streamer like eight months ago
He shall remain nameless, but you know I get this I went to that streamer and I told them
Hey, um, let's, you know, get rid of the cancer out of your show and just try to revive it
Let's try to get it back to where it was and get everybody back, you know, get it to where it was
Well, yeah, but it's like I mean even that I mean even when I was at it's like the most people there a lot of those were trolls
That I didn't care for you know no no no, but you're gonna get a track the right people right and so that's the whole thing
And there are people out there and those people away
We're getting these mini Manson and vagina pictures all day
Oh here it is it says
says the copyright strikes are on the way ads and they're like on the way it's time to get you
offline beta wins beta wins beta wins ha ha who do you think that that is doing that if you had
to guess i mean reason beg beat it for forgiveness okay not hold on hold on oh they keep coming
bro damn i don't i don't know why i don't know why she was on modded uh oh yeah because i'm on
But I guess so she's done with me now, I guess too because she's on monitor, but I don't moderate
It's just like I'm on my other channel now. Oh, who are you coming up? Oh, I know you
Iron X is another cancer
That's another fucking cancer, bro. I next bro. Maybe it is time to say and it says you got dog
It says she has never done anything. You are a monster fake
Jew F. A. G. Beated in that picture mini Manson with a razor blade near their vagina. Oh my god
How disgusting, bro?
But anyway, yeah
Yeah, dude, cuz I did that one another screamer dude
I like eight months ago
I try to get them to get their shit back on track get rid of the cancer which you know
At least you got rid of the cancer that mother screamer didn't they didn't listen to me
And then it's just going down now because they didn't listen, but you you got rid of the cancer
You
No, no, no, all you got to do is just get clear of them
Yeah, you do apologize to the certain people that you need to apologize to like that. Did you ever like say like
Like have you taken accountability for
Reality would you would you really want that do you want it comes back to that to how would I say?
the people you want listening, the people that are ready for the right reasons.
I called her Shrek for like weeks and everything, but then she was doing...
Well, she does kind of look like Shrek, so it kind of looks like Shrek.
It was a perfect analogy and stuff.
Yeah, she does look like Shrek.
He just annoyed the fuck out of everybody because he's annoying.
He's a troll.
He fucking like goes around trying to get attention for himself
and like destroy other people.
Yeah, that branding key, right?
No, I didn't look he look he did he spoke on her child. I didn't okay. Yeah, see he's disgusting. See
Then he started talking about her her son
Thank you. He started talking about her son, bro
Reformitizing shit with a mom, but I don't know anything about who they are anything. I don't really care about that kind of stuff
And yeah, yeah, I have nothing to do with the show
About oh, you know, it's something about dwarf and something that's not even true. She said so it's like what?
No, no, no, um
It is true, bro. She does how well she she does
Normal normal for dwarf size, but I don't know about you know
Okay, I'm sorry
So I mean he said that but it's like then but he he also put up a picture
I think about Alexander's father with like a red ball on his mouth and I kicked him off right away
He even put up Clemsey's uh
His kids picture the other day. Yeah, see
No, no not the ball. Well, yeah the ball went to but he put up the other one the the kicks picture remember when he was up there
And that gets so sick and I mean it's like why are you I mean
What is that about that is some kind of like that is like especially if you're like
You know people are already saying that like why are you like I'm gonna be your daughter's window and stuff like that's scary
Yeah, dude, dude, dude, then you want to be flashing weapons and shit like that and
I can I can shoot again. I sound like peewee, but I shoot like Rambo
Do this guy sounds like he's 19 years old. He's like he's never hit puberty
You know, I thought he was like 34
Oh dude 34 dude and this guy does he live by himself or does he kind of
Kind of give me a lowdown. How did he come? I see cuz I wasn't
Okay
He said like, you know, he kept getting like people would kick him out and stuff and then
And then he like came on panel and it was kind of like I don't know
And then everyone started going crazy and saying do you do it? Don't have him on don't yeah
I know okay. I totally agree, but you know what there you go
I'm so the so the innocent are now being attacked on my on my side and I never attacked anybody
Right and but then nobody cares right because I deserve it like karma, right?
So what where I was I know Lisa's just for what I think he was in there. You think he I think he was dating her I
Was I mean yeah, I mean I've been here that we've been in there at the same time
I but I didn't know was him at the time in there, but he got kicked out
So he came he just started like as a chatter
Yeah, you're so you open your you welcome arms, right you open your arms, you know like the way you are
with anybody yeah with anybody you know you always give the better for the doubt before you're not
going to guess oh you're this and this and that without any you know concrete evidence of proof or
anything like that you know
I'm just kidding, no, I'm just kidding, um, yeah, hey, that was your impression of brandon keel?
Years ago, yeah, he, I mean, he's crazy. He always like, oh, this, this woman's in love with me,
This desirable status when he's like, you know
Do you come from the Carter verse? Did he come from there? I don't believe so
Because I've seen a music video that Alex did kind of cuz gamble kind of did but the gamble was a troll brand
I'm sorry of a
Aaron and then he became a troll Brandon after Aaron died. He used to be you know what here's what happened
gamble sent Aaron Carter this like
uh this firm request on instagram and then each then he said his name then he said it was like a
15 year old girl and then he asked for a dick pic and i guess erin had sent a pic and so then he's
like you're a pedophile erin and then all of a sudden now brandon takes um a page from his book
and tries to do it on my show where brandon pretends to be like uh like this dumb person in the chat
and and then like can i have a mod please and eventually when they're modded they're like
you bought it a child yeah he tried to use that last time and i was like no sake wouldn't mod again
uh i know i'm i know i was modding a three four year old weirdo yes i was playing with you like a
Do you give all the norgas or what trick what who's the one who grabbed the
Remember when they came in well, they all come in right with their different little if they come in with the mouse
It's not one of them right? You know
Like Lola likes to catch one once in a while Rudy has caught one once, but I'm okay
They jump on my table and drop the mouse right in front of me
So gross I went and throw it away, but it's like
Oh, yeah, you threw it away. How'd you throw it? You pick it up by its tail
No, I get the dust pan.
Oh, OK, you got it, like, with the broom and stuff.
OK.
Oh, OK.
Throw it in the trash, and then it's gone.
So people are like, oh my god, all the all these cats eat are like carcasses of dead animals and stuff and they're starving and
And and all your cats they're you need to fix your cats all my cats are fix
Do their inside outside cats that you can't help it if they you know
They can that's their primal nature when they go outside. They're gonna hunt because that's you know, they're in skis
regardless if you feed them, you know
Inside food, they're still gonna go ahead and hunt outside. You know, they're gonna get a bird
You think like wearing clothes and living indoors is like a natural state of affairs for like, you know an animal
It's like, you know, no, that's something we we do because we can but
Animals like you know they'll go in a cave or they'll go under a tree or something like that or you know
There's different things, but usually they're in nature and stuff not
He's ever brain damage. That's why he's dumb doesn't explain his sex. Well, I don't know maybe maybe he has had a little too hard or something
I don't know. He's he's bizarre here. He had brain
Yeah, dude I got is highly autistic bro
Brandon Q is like an autistic brother. Dude, I'm just like so he came
So you came over here you got cool
Would you kind of explain the side of the story and stuff like that?
And it would have ended there, but then Alexander does this like this show and she's like, oh
What about psyche you having brandy Q on and then she gave a my show we had to talk about it
And I was like well Tony's telling me how to have a month
So I'm not really interested with Tony as they'll judge for myself. I don't really know all the lore whatever
But it's like it doesn't the stuff I've seen and not yeah, you're gonna interview him yourself
You're gonna find out that for your own give your own judgment. Yeah
I will I roll the beach, but uh, I need to put my mosquitoes still on the wash right now
Yeah, I can I're on the beach, but it's I don't know if it's like oh my god
I got a little overcast, but uh, it looks like it's gonna be cold outside. Do you like I am a good
I'm gonna do your lifeguards. I'm living where you don't know. This is where junior lifeguards are the
Baywatch was filmed. Oh, okay. Well, wait the old school one or the new one with the rock. I mean, probably both
I mean, it's like
Okay
Yeah, I was just really chirping out like
This morning those videos man like I'm not gonna talk about it. I'm just like beyond anything. It's like really insane. It's a really
I mean, she was like, in this dark, you can just see the whites of her eyes.
He's like, sorry, Peter, I'm so sorry, you were right.
He's a spiritual rapist.
I mean, it's like, God.
What does that even mean, does that mean it's like I'm not because I don't understand, doesn't make sense, there's aren't even real things.
So she woke up just to go live and talk about that.
And then she says I'm going to go back to sleep now.
Well I think the demon must have woken up for half an hour.
It's crazy, it's craziness, it's really crazy.
Anybody that's watching from the outside
will be able to see that, right?
It's like there's already enough of a pattern established.
So, but now I am starting to figure things out.
It's like, give or see, I'm the wicker man,
you ever see that movie?
Yeah.
Okay, well the first time you watch it,
like the one for the 70s on the Nicholas Cage one,
but the first time you watch it,
you're like, what's going on?
I don't know what's happening
because you're kind of like there's a mystery to it, right?
Yeah, you kind of figure out what's going on.
You see her, she starts being, oh, that was this, that meant that, that meant that.
So now I'm starting to see all these things, like even going back to her appearance when she said
like the N word a hundred times and called RG and N word and said he was gonna shoot him between the
eyes and all this. Oh gosh, no. And so, and then now they're friends. I mean now they're friends,
they hate me. So it's like, I mean, it's like, talk about hate bonding.
Hate bonding is pretty much the worst way, the worst thing to base a relationship on because
If they're already going back and forth, then they're probably gonna go back and forth again
and then we're gonna hate mom with them
and it's gonna be an area to abuse these guys.
Everything comes back around on full swing, you know, it's like, um, you know, so just, you know, start doing good.
Samman's hitting that. I don't know what he's hitting.
Samman, all Samman's hitting is, uh, a chopped cheese sandwich with his teeth.
You and I trip on how KZ fake this fucking death.
Well, he did it with the assistance of RG and like, you know, they, I don't know if there's a news article, they're like, I have the obituary, I don't know about that.
I, I've seen a couple of people post it up before. So I was tripping out.
The obituary?
Yeah, there was a legit one where he was that supposedly like in the jail, like.
Like he like OD or something like that like on fentanyl or something like that
I know his name. See the thing is like emperors Janet was on last year and like they started saying she ate her dog
And then our g came up. He's like, I have a police. I have a newspaper article or police report
Police report police report was like typed in like cursive or something. It was like didn't look right. It was like
I was like, why is it in this weird font?
It could be doctored up. It could be photoshop. It was because it was all about the wrong dates were wrong
It was about someone eating a dog in their backyard and person didn't eat her dog. I mean, I mean, it's just so sick
Yeah
I don't know. It's like, you know, it's just like, you know, don't do I mean I didn't the thing is
The first the first time she said, you know, she's woke up the friendship or whatever
It was over pretty much nothing, but I had questioned her about something. I questioned her
intentions or something like that or her
And so she's she got so mad and then that was it a spiritual trafficker. I was a demon worshiper
I don't know a cult leader
What she called you got what else was it?
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, a frog a frog dude. I like almost everything under the sunlight
Again, I'll tell you here's like the list of things that she accuses me of like recently
I mean, it's like it's like it's like the police like Charles Manson's biographies
so
Crazy, I mean this is like this is like people in jail for a hundred years would have the kind of it's kind of a
Analysis so it says it says what is it? What am I being accused of?
criminal, exploitative, greedy, abusive liar, drug addict, I live in a drug den.
Let's see, I've given preferential treatment. I have been capable of employment.
There's been property damage because of me.
All he wants to do is gain his apartment.
be online on YouTube and smoke cannabis and get alcohol
Send me those white clothes that she's had the picture. Oh, so she contributed to the
And then she took a picture of it saying look, he's a drunk. I mean, that's the kind of
That wasn't a troll but that wasn't a fucking troll move man, I don't know what is because that was like a big
75% troll 25% a real person do that. That's like saying I'm gonna send you a donation and send you a donation
They try to say look at see I there's the receipt that
Exploded her dead, you know her grieving process to get money out of her. So I never asked her for a dime ever
My dad died two years ago, I'm so I
Feel like I'm being exploited by her. Hey, what's up, Arthur? I'm sorry, but I think Chris delay is lying
Got to be honest about what about the whole you know passing of the parents
Well, we don't know when she has this history of kind of like this. Um, what would you do?
Supposedly had a baby before remember and it was like a like one of those little
Yeah, it was a toy like an expensive like lifelike toy
$1,000 like doll that looks like it was like a
miscarried
She gave it away to Macy's and Macy's
raised him to mannequin.
You know how crazy that is though?
That she had to lie about something crazy like that.
Or maybe, you know, maybe she's not lying.
Maybe she said, one of my parents passed away.
Period. That's it. She didn't say when.
Well, I know it. No, I know when they did
She bonded with me over or both of our fathers passed away from cancer like and you know
And then she's like oh, and he my father was gay and you're gay and like I'm learning about gay people through
My father like through you and stuff and I want to like learning into my dad like I don't know just like she was thinking I an expert
Having a conversation with her dad and taping and stuff and then she's saying oh, that's the biggest violation
But she was thanking her like the day before that's a beautiful phone call. I could hear her voice. So maybe she's not lying
But there's two but there's too many things that she's saying. I mean, it's like they're all these opposite things
I don't know. You didn't hear me. Oh shit. I guess I lost signal, but I was saying um
Maybe she said okay. Yeah, he passed away, but she's not giving the detail of what?
You know, I know he passed away last year, I mean it's like, but the thing is like, I never said anything about him or made fun of him or anything, but he's acting like I'm like, I did something, but she's talking about my passed away father, you know, saying, oh, he must, he's a terrible parent, and you know, all that and this stuff, you know, he's going after like
Roy, Roy, Roy
Right and hey, you know what you get in American labs. Oh funny funny's happen to psyche first of all you can see can think
Oh, it's karma or whatever really what did I do to warrant this like and what if this was in your life?
And if you did what I you did what I did with that warrant that happened to you and if it did
Nobody deserves a period right? That's what I think
It doesn't matter man or woman. He's right around and it's just beginning like she's God. Are you God bitch?
I mean it's like she's like oh your farmers just beginning
My life has been a continuation of cause and effect.
So it's all karma, it's not just beginning.
Okay, and you know what?
People that do that kind of shit to people,
like bad shit to people on purpose, that's bad karma.
Not somebody that's innocent and getting attacked
and innocent people being attacked, understand?
Yeah, what up J-Dig?
I'm J-Dog.
What's poppin', what's poppin'?
Alex, no, no, no, we're not Alex though.
out there Alexander McQueen with my well what happened with Alexander McQueen my most pro as
his profile picture and like and stuff like that and he's and he's like fucking doing that shit
and like he lost his mind yeah and he has to he's in love with what he wants to be Alexander's
baby daddy and stuff so he's like you know he sat there and literally in her chat one night for
He's like, oh, my little Alexander, reading of Mary.
He didn't love it there.
Oh, my god, give the people the characters up
in this motherfucker, Arthur.
I need to write a movie.
By the way, guys, I do have a movie coming out.
You have to see this.
This is really cool.
Is it an amateur video?
No, it's not a video.
It's just that I just have the poster for it already.
Roy, Roy.
You want to see the poster, Arthur?
My new movie?
Scared as a boy it is a picture of you and me. This is gonna be AI
Arthur just walking. We're gonna spoil it Arthur
Listen, here's what it is. Well, you know, I'm proud of you. I like I've been listening to your stream
I don't think you do AI songs anymore, huh? I do I started with one, but here. Oh boy. No, no
Just set it.
Just have some self-awareness.
Like, there's a whole-
Arthur, you lost your mod.
You lost your mod.
Arthur, how long was that?
Arthur, ten minutes?
Dude, you didn't even wrench me.
I didn't know that.
I did so.
Okay, okay, sorry.
I'll be quiet.
Thank you.
You're gonna be nice to me.
I'm actually, like, not like the fucking devil.
Thank you.
I'm just born under that sign of capricorn, which is what it does.
Okay, you're welcome.
You see it.
okay yes it's amazing wow thank you okay yeah it's beautiful it's a golden wrench i had it i had a
Okay, good.
i had a i actually had a bronze for you man look at the bronze bird your head
My god
Don't say his name. He might show up
Well, I mean he is so lame. I mean it's like he's wrong. We're talking about white night
I mean here. Can we agree? Christine's probably watching too from
Right here. I'm right here after
Christine smoke eight packs of cigarettes a day. Oh, yeah, look at that's the poster right there
Oh, yeah, that's a good picture psyche. Oh, yeah
Hi, I'm your twin sister
to
That looks like a marble. I know I'm like a superhero
Arthur gonna be Christine Christine
Arthur you get out of here out. I think he lost signal man
the community timing is terrible.
Dude, what happened to your tooth not being mean as curious
and noticeably, does anything happen to your tooth?
You lose a tooth.
No.
Okay.
I saw, I saw like, I think clumsy's entire like bottom jaw
came out of his mouth one night or something.
I'm sure here he's not.
Yeah.
Oh, you come back.
I love, I love a little bit of the statement.
Yeah.
What about me?
Hey, it's Christine.
Hey, you're walking here.
I don't know why you want to take this panel.
Yeah, oh, yeah, that's either Christine's voice or like a New York construction worker, right?
I don't know. Yeah, but who else? I saw somebody that's bald. Yeah, so all these bald things on me. I mean, it's like, I think bald is beautiful, but
Why if they do me with like this like shaved head with like a mullet in the back
And it's like I have no you they try to make him look like okay Arthur don't they have you ever seen
Herald and Kumar Arthur
Okay, do you know the tow truck driver?
I know but that's how they try to make him look but he don't look nothing like that
No psyche
Oh, Samman does look like the truck driver of, you know, yeah, he does too. Yeah. I mean,
geez, it's called a Skullet. Yeah, I don't have a Skullet. I have actually a nice head of hair
and I don't have gray hair yet. I mean, I have red beard a little bit, but my hair's fine.
Samman ball, a big fan. They have a picture, literally.
She hates Tommy James, but in her A.I. Tommy James muscular at the Juggalo boxers.
When I recall the same, you want to take him home because of why? Because you guys were
thinking about the A.I. deal and brain when I sexually assault a Juggalo now and you're going
to get the Juggalos after us. I mean, geez. What does that mean?
Are you down with the hatchet or not, I don't know.
Can Sandman call in here?
Yeah, he's welcoming me.
He's a bitch.
I usually kick him off within a few minutes.
I don't know.
Like, when I'm up here, I don't think so.
Dude, I think Tommy James is associated with juggalos.
Because last time when I was on Tommy James' panel,
he had a boy blue up there.
And boy blue.
What, a juggalos?
Oh, this is embalding, call the hair clipper men.
First of all, the hair clipper men,
I'm not just the client, I'm the president.
The second of all, sweet pea.
You in the chat?
I'm balding
Having a hairline like a regular hairline. It's not ball. It's not gone back an inch
You're lucky to have
Balding and she pulls her hair back and she looks like you know, she looks like a professional wrestler
You remember in the beginning when you were on be this panel and she was like trying to flash
And if she kept putting her hair like in front of herself like that I try to hide
over I don't understand with it but it's a comb over she said the comb over is not working this is a
comb over like a comb over means she's from an older generation a bald spot on your head you see a
beta would be covering her hair like this in the beginning she would be trying to flash psyche
like that on her panel remember when remember when that happened i think i was like what is your
hair all in front of her face yeah yeah she had like a veil like a like a black veil like
i thought she was like trying to like distract
She was like trying to distract, but like trying to show like like cleavage and shit like the whole like
Do she cause your window to get broken it was her fault
Yeah, I think she broke it was just her voice
Dude it was her fault
She woke up the neighbors made the neighbors man of psyche saying that psyche was yelling when he wasn't
Yeah, it wasn't even and it was like the weekend too, so it wasn't even like a work night or anything like that like
Yeah, and the neighbor got pissed off and like I was like, what the fuck
Yeah, the picture. Yeah, I mean just deal with it. I mean, it's like what you're gonna call me out for balding
The next time you call me for balding
I'm gonna start, you know doing and be the AIs of her balding and that's gonna be your fall
That's your mistress, right?
What up, sweet pea, you fucking bitch? How you doing? Long time!
Yeah, are you secretly in love with sweet pea Arthur? She's cool. She's cool. She's cool people. Yes. We I want to see what she looks like now like like
I want to see that I know seeing the picture of her back then in 2009 or eight whatever year that was
She looks about my age so if she if that was because she says that she that time
She looks like she's probably around our age. Yeah
Guys you see a bald spot look at the look at even like the where the bald spots should be is that a comb over it?
I mean is there a bald spot anywhere? It's like I don't know. I just see I just see the your hair
You're the pot you I just see your part, you know where you make your line
You know how you separate your the fact that I'm sick of telling you that I'm not bald bitch
But you keep saying it so okay get used to it if you're gonna keep fishing out
You got to take it bitch that picture was two years ago you fucking retard. I'm sick of you telling me that
I'm baldy KZ KZ. Let me not let me not show your picture. Okay, KZ. Let's do it KZ
Okay, yeah, we're gonna show your picture now KZ. This is you on camera. You come on cameras. It's not dogs
You're anything look at this is you
This is for this person insulting my looks right here. Look at this person
Look at this person
You
He looks like
No, he was hoping but he know he's alive
He's alive he came on panel he really is alive
Got to see him right now dude. Can you come on? Can you come on? Is he a lot on panel psychic?
They're being summoned. Is he a lot on panel?
My friend God body reigns. Um, he's like very good looking and he like took off his hat and he's completely bald like a cute
He's like your your hair. He's like
But I was like, wow bald is sexy. He makes bald look sexy, but he's it's kind of fun. It's kind of shocking because you're like
Wait, hold on dude. If he's alive, you know how crazy that is
Why is he crazy? He faked his gut. He tried to troll everybody, but nobody cared
You're allowed anywhere you want but everyone's ignores you right?
Okay, okay
KZ wrote sweety the creepiest fucking stop yeah
Now friends again, right? I think it's fine. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I know you're that those looks you give to you know
He was dating Emma Levi-tan and they were married you for like what was it like 15 years ago?
Use a whole person
Jay dog is that
I'm gonna put the customer service in the middle. We're gonna do an Eiffel Tower review, Arthur.
There you go.
Oh, hi.
Is that working?
Right there you go.
You did an Eiffel Tower on purpose.
Yeah, hold on.
You're starting to get weak, bro.
I have it on full blast and it's not even that cold.
Uh-oh.
You hear what happened in New York, right? Remember the surge?
Oh guys, what happened in your power search how now, but this is my car though the cars
AC is going out to these two Russians
Russians climb the Empire State Building and put a flag on top of it. Yeah, that was crazy, huh?
I'm jealous of your full head of hair. I'm jealous of your your your full your full body of fat you 400 pound pigs
Your AC system your AC system has to be recharged. You got it. You need coolant or you got a
No, you got to take it into a mechanic because it's pressurized and you don't have probably don't have the tools for it
And you won't know what kind to put in there. So yeah, it's best to take it to mechanic
Adversary relationship at the end of the day, we know we're not like we know we don't really hate each other
We're just like we'd love to hate each other, but everybody else I
Hold on. So I have a straight question for you. Yes
What?
In Sweet Pea would allow you and she'd be okay with me.
Would you fuck her?
I don't know what she looks like.
I see in the picture what she looks like.
I want to see what she looks like now.
I want to see if she's really hot like that.
You know what, fuck it.
Psyche, you gotta fuck kill Mary.
Bita, Christine and Sweet Pea, go.
I kill myself
Ladies and gentlemen
When you get rid of Brandon Q like you just revive yourself
Hey, dude, why would you kill I just kill them all
Yeah, it's okay, we love being clipped
Like you do you mind being clipped bro, are you like it free publicity bro
I should be, you know what, before I do that, I would speak to you first.
I would be, I would, yeah, I would take, I would take the, I'd take the K and I'd just do KKK, kill, kill, kill.
And then I, I had a K for myself.
Wow, you should go jump off a bridge, but with the, with the, with the harness, Sweet Pea, the harness,
and the professional bridge jumping is the Olympic sport Christine told me all about it.
I didn't know.
KZ, do you want to come on the panel bro? Let's talk.
KZ.
I want your ass over.
KZ, there's useless ass up here, bitch.
I'm walking here I'm walking here you case it but Casey's homeless
He's a drug addict. He's a drug addict.
Yes, he came on panel, he talked with his psyche.
She wants to be, I want to be friends with Vita now. I want to be friends.
I don't like hate bonding, but I'm gonna hate bond with everybody.
Okay, okay. Wow. Okay, the turtles.
What oh, yeah, Arthur did you know that devil lies is buried the turtle what?
Yeah, and Samantha Avery is Kate
No, I kind of figured it out well for one a long time ago like when I first came into communities like a long long time ago
Kate fucked up by letting somebody else know
And then I said I was in the cat and I read it so that's how I figured out about it
I would just I didn't even see me in the car. I was just you know a lot of cats
I'll just be in the cat and I won't even say anything and I'll just be there just watching and so yeah people
Do watch what you say because I will be watching
and you beat it you are okay you be you hate bond it was be over be that stuff like that right
and you were in a queue and then it's like but you're still mad because
so I don't get it now why she mad at chrysaland if chrysaland is trying to pick up with be that
okay I don't know I don't know because I think she likes you she has a crush on Kate why don't why
don't Samantha Avery come up because then magically last night on cake show
Oh, thank you, Samantha Avery, for gifting some membership.
I mean, I love talking about Boston Brigitte, I love talking about Boston Brigitte.
Gifting her own membership on her own channel.
I just post what he said about Boston Brigitte.
Oh, oh, oh, no.
Oh, you fuck Boston Brigitte.
That fucks down.
No, fuck Boskinberg it what we're good on Boskinberg it like
What does she bring to the cable legit? What does she really bring what a funny accent a couple of funny voices like?
Tick she don't even come up
No on the shorts when I talk about the short we're like like come on video and like like do that shit like at least
Entertain like that like be some kind of eye candy if she is any which I doubt
But
She could come on paneling yeah, you see I don't know why they don't fucking don't do that
Like why don't these fucking women use their assets to their advantage? I don't understand that I really don't they don't care
They don't care, but they think their voices are asset like what the fuck like even Alex Alex at least cams up like and she shows
What she's working with
And then the other who else does it again? Well, who's another female? Oh, Trisha. She's sweet. I
Well, I would like to see sweet peek him up
Maybe you should just want to convince them. It's just just just or be like a muscle moment
Just put the full burqa on so we don't have to look at you. I mean jeez
I mean that's what be no does she wants a full burqa on she don't want nobody to see and only the privilege can see her
Like oh you can only see me of your privilege to gain my trust and be in my little inner circle of you know
simps and followers
Why does Boston Bridget always hide her forehead in her selfies?
Well, she's missing hair.
She fucked up.
She let it slip in somebody else's chat.
And again, J-Dog was around and nobody knew I was there.
And she was explaining to another female in that chat
that she has to use a special kind of shampoo
to kind of help the hair grow in the back of her hair
because she's losing hair at her age.
So yeah.
Well, I mean, it's like she's
See people give themselves up they could they just be chatting away into in a public chat and they don't even know
Bridges worth with other means with her, you know completely bald like they make him me all day. I mean, it's like and they all do
I mean, it's like, you know, I got on tape Alexander saying, well, you don't look like that
We're just fucking with you because I'm I was just trolling and you know
And I should say I trolled the fuck out of you and you did a great job because you know you survived
I don't know how you survived me survived
I'll still survive. You know, I'm a survivor, right? The shampoos call it mookie.
Okay
I'm lurking he's actually you're lurking Jada's on the panel. It's not lurking. Yeah, KZ
Yeah, KZ is so scared to come on panel like he's a pussy. Well, you better come on panel KZ
Caprici you ain't gonna have nowhere else to go
No, he is he came on panel and he talked to everybody. Yeah
It was not AI
All he was in Skype or something. No, it wasn't Skype. He legit came on the panel like
Yeah, he even explained why he even explained why he did it he thought it would be funny and but the backfired on him cuz nobody gave a shit
You're the only one who you're the one and you're the one out of the 99% who dare
Yeah
He says he comes in with these jokes. What jokes does KZ bring to the table nothing
And then he screams like he's like he's already screaming out like he's like, oh, this is all group beat out
We're the way we're in the kitty game
Like gang and the gang don't want him
Yeah, yeah, he said it was my community, remember he said it was my community
I'm a kiddie. Dude, he was going so hard that day fighting for his right to be online
Hell yeah, I mean, they're gonna make psyche break out the speedo is you're saying about American flag
You know you're kind of hinting at that Arthur. I mean, you don't you don't shine just like you know, you want to see him
Yeah
Somebody either
Arthur get your AC give out
It's showing us some colder air now. It took a little while, but I'm definitely gonna take it to the weekend
One second. I'll take care of one thing real quick. Okay
How much did they charge for some show like this?
Picture ACS just give me what are you in the East Coast?
Yeah, it's gonna charge you up pretty penny. Especially during the Seatway
Well, here's a really sad thing. It's like I guess this like I don't know if I should even say it
But I guess it's all over now, but
That's okay. That's okay. I won't say it. I just got a very interesting all I want to say the letters from but here
Let's say let's say I for the
Hypothetically
Hypothetically, I apologize to a person after several several times and then actually was really nice about it really genuine. I really don't
Ever care to hear from you again? You're a narcissistic, backstabbing, two-faced
POS that needs to explain the lies, the doxing, the I'm only sorry till I do it again.
Talking shit constantly lying about bleep and hold on and as well as many others.
till you get what you want just to start the only reason you're sorry is so bleep comes back well
that's on her she knows um where i stand that absolutely not with you ever you have two years
of chances time to man up even though you're new i don't love you stop telling me you love me because
but yourself idea for you off touch grass get off drugs go see a
shrink as you clearly need one for all your personalities you went
too far and I guess you pushed me and pushed me and I like it
here or give yourself the hell is going on reading something you
got forgive yourself that for me to forgive you will absolutely
happen when pigs fly upside down people in hell get ice water
mother can fly where I'm going you made your bed now lie in it
be a sob. They'd stop fucking lying about me saying, if you tried to fucking contact
me when you didn't do, nor ever speak to me again, fuck you and have a good day.
Oh, here, I'll give you a hint of who said that.
Can I get a ham sandwich for my birthday?
Oh, wow.
The porky from a toy store.
No, no, no.
I know who you said, really?
Wow.
Ham sandwich girl.
I gave my codex, it came up, Ham Sandwich Girl,
her name.
Really?
Well, I mean.
Yeah, okay, so I'm sorry to the other person
But you saw this joke me and that's how she talks to me. Okay, and listen you keep telling me to apologize
I might like it bitch you better be careful Arthur. He'll take you up on that
And then like American history X type shit fucking put your mouth on a carbon fucking
Oh my god, as long as you're dicks on it.
Whoa, yo, what the fuck?
See, I can't be doing that shit, dude.
Nah, nah, you gotta chill.
I want to eat your castrated penis.
Whoa, what the?
Oh my gosh.
Oh my goodness.
Put that with a fucking napkin.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna eat the napkin.
Hey, you know, there's a bird in France, and they eat this bird, it's like a little songbird, but they eat it.
You're aware of that.
Like they I mean they kill it and it's like it is like under but they they feel so bad eating it
In the dark and put like a napkin over the plate and stuff and they can't see it
And you didn't they eat in the dark. Wow
Like a French thing. Have you ever heard that? No, I've never heard of that at all
Really weird
Just gonna gloss over saying the wildest shit that's right. Well, it's for entertainment purposes only. Yeah. Yeah, there you go
Okay, so it's called an Ortulian
Ortulian bunting. Okay, so I'll find out like a little thing about it a bunty a bunting and so this is a
Just a minute long, but you have to see this. This is a ritual of eating a tiny Ortolian. So this is crazy
Check out the the Ortolian. This is what they eat in France. It's a little French songbird
Yeah, I thought it was the funniest thing right now man, I'm gonna be a tradition.
And a controversial health boost.
In French cuisine the Ortolan, a tiny bird served whole, was once considered the pinnacle
of luxury.
But there's a twist, diners traditionally eat it under a napkin to fully savor the experience
in secret.
Why the napkin?
Some say it's to trap the aromas while others believe it's to shield your moment of indulgence
But this ritual isn't for the faint-hearted, you eat everything, bones and all.
Ortle and meat is rich in protein and healthy fats, while its tiny bones provide calcium
and essential minerals.
Each bite is said to deliver a dense, nutrient-packed experience.
Some diners even claimed it boosted their vitality and improved digestion, making it
not just a delicacy, but a functional food.
The Ordolyn population in France plummeted, leading to strict laws in 1999 to protect
the species.
Today, enjoying this delicacy is almost impossible, legally at least.
Despite the ban, food lovers and chefs alike still dream of the Ordolyn's unique taste
and nutritional benefits.
If you had the chance, would you try it, bones and all?
Tag someone who'd risk it all for a bite of the forbidden.
No
Wow, that's disgusting. No, it's very crazy, huh?
You like eat this full bird under the snack in
Dude, I was crazy. You don't know what I thought was funny, bro. What's this up? Why don't I just?
It's got to go and knock in on the guns. They could say if I wanted to show up at somebody, you know who lives around
Let's just say you're gonna go knock on beaters door, and I'm not gonna knock on door
Let's just say I want to get a post getting off. I don't know if I want to I'm not gonna go anywhere
Like I'm already I'm already being called the stalker and stuff. I know not you not you. Not you. I said hypothetically
The Minecraft GTA GTA and Super Mario Brothers right there
And you know don't even I'm not even gonna knock on the door. Let's just say
It's kind of just somebody knocking on the door
Somebody just put a post-it note on the door and just ask me to get it and then just leave the post-it note there
Actually, you gotta get going even put nothing on it. You leave it there
and then later on a stream
Just ask her. Hey beat a gig you get that post get no
Okay, okay, my bad. Okay
Yeah
So do you like something you can pop for in here?
There you go.
Oh
Okay, if you report this I'm gonna report every single one of your videos
Yeah, your friend beat his bald head exactly how about that? Yeah, and and Boston Bridgett Boston Bridgett beat in sweet B
You're even your sour sour B
Swat you with the fly way who is lady back three inside the chat
Here because she's blocked everywhere. Yeah, okay. Well, I'm but I can't see her either because I don't just like
Already tried you did it succeed. Whoa
You can get to that can try again
Report dude, we're talking in Minecraft. We're not saying nobody you just saying like we were just you know
And then you told me to be you know, you don't want to talk about that real name. I mean geez
Yeah, it was Beetlejuice. We're talking about Beetlejuice like
Yeah, yeah, there's not that we didn't say no last name
Like war let's fucking go. Well, what are you gonna strike me on cuz I'm not doing anything wrong. Yeah, I didn't do nothing
Well, we're talking about something completely different
It's just meant for bullying that's when a strike war just for the fun of it completely dedicated just on on terrorizing psyche
That's all that's all. Yeah, that's why she made the channel, right?
Yeah, I don't even see I don't see the little battery
So he's talking about kids ask I think
Oh, no, he shapes her butt. She had like a diaper rash all over her ass from the razor bumps
I'm kind of fucking I should like cottage cheese, bro
Kate's ass was not smooth, bro. I should have like dimples me
You ever seen them prostitutes when they walk like what their big old ass is? Well, I don't know on the part of LA, but like
Let's say a bigger row is three or let's say we go on on Whittier Boulevard
And you're gonna see them prostitute a big ass fat prostitute, but then they have all the cellulite. That's what cakes
I'm gonna start with a rash
You inspected as she said well, I mean, it's like, you know, I think it's a whole body in there
It's that kid. Well, I'm stuck in
Double does it's a bed
Yeah, there you go
That's crazy. It's like yeah, I gotta head out bro. I'll hit you up later. Right, bro. Peace out
Yeah
Yeah, oh, I'm really scared. Oh, no my YouTube account's gone. What I don't have to deal with fucking fucking Kate again
Me fucking so happy when I'm fucking dumb as this account fucking out of here
I have to deal with the thousands of trolls that just abused me and bullied me, you know 24-7 and don't don't fucking do shit for me
I'll be really upset. Oh, I'm so scared
Try me bitch with that. Oh, yeah, so there's a good song. I actually posted the other day. I hope you like it
It's not mine. It's they got it's from this band. I like but I can play it
Because I don't you'll see it
Actually, it really fits right now
You I seem triggered. Well, you seem enormous
You keep barking my name
Like it means something to me, but honestly, I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck
And talk that shit like you know my soul
Building fake stories just to play a role
Mad cause I call out every crooked game
Then cry out when I say a name
You'll mistake cause my weakness too long to the calm and me f-
I get grace gave patience gave understanding now you got the storm you demanded don't ever corner me an extra prize when the fire finally likes
My eyes I'll protect my peace with sharpened teeth and buried disrespect underneath
See how fast this angel since you want to
Behind closed doors
When the chaos
Like you hold down like me thought I'd break
Thought I'd kneel, give it